Tell me how you think I'm wrong When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love You erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know When I give away my trust
Tell me how I'm
But this is my show. I get to play whatever song I want and you can go fuck yourself, okay? Bye
Anyway, what's up guys? Hi KZ. Hi chibi chibi. How are you guys doing? I got some coffee
Yeah, I mean it's like yeah, oh, let's be the first commenter. I have a two-minute song so I can like you know
You know get things ready for
What the fuck are idiots? I mean, get a life. Go get a life. Stop being obsessed with buying.
Um, global stack, um, let's see, hold on.
You want to get kicked out too? Hold on.
I think I'm playing. I think I'm playing.
Let's see.
but it was time you up with that.
And you don't have to have long.
Maybe a minute, might be a day, so check it back.
So I've got good shit to say.
I've got a show to do, and it's like,
what, are you gonna start out negative, guys?
Do I even wanna share my stories?
I got some stories.
You don't wanna hear about the secret freak-off last night?
You don't wanna hear that?
That's okay.
I'll wait for more people to get here.
Everyone wants to fuck with me like you know first thing in the morning. I'm trying to like oh, I'll go on on air
I'll do a good show
Pending for the n-word and then consulting my you know, DJ Electros video
No, I said to his end says and I was like excited to start
Yeah, I don't know. I'll leave it for now.
Oh.
Anyway.
Hi, hi, everybody else.
We're not going to, it's just like fucking, I was like, oh, you know, I fucking got coffee bagels.
Set up the book and book and everything and it's like we're gonna start with this
I've got shit to tell you I got shit to tell you and you'll it's exciting
I mean, it's like but just go away if you know if you're not gonna support the show go away
Not you but yeah, hi booty bandit
It's like go fuck yourself if you're like in a you know, or just like you know, you can just sit in the
Purgatory which is like basically you just can't talk. That's what they want. It's okay. I'll give them what they want
I like that. I'd like to deliver but they want to be blocked now. I don't think so
Unfortunately, I can't block. Actually, I can't block to go for my entire show. There's some people I, you know, oh
Fucking lucky. Wait till you hear. What do you hear the stories? What do you hear the stories? I got stories to tell. Hey, Jamie
Jamie my little
Let's see, let's see Rapper, that's gonna be, that's gonna be, no you can't be mad and why are you asking Loki, oh no no, are you asking Loki, Loki can't give you mod, only I can okay, Loki's like a second angel in command, I'm God here okay, it's okay Jimmy.
Yeah, oh come on. It is wonderful
Yeah, I mean
Both gosh, okay, so I don't know. I don't even know where to start
But I'm just gonna let people come on in for a minute. I got this is a vanilla hazelnut
Hold on for my nails. Okay guys on my nails. Okay. I know apparently I'm like, you know, I can you know spread
HIV with these fingernails, you know
Apparently according to the comment I heard about a hundred times last night. Okay, but we'll get to that. We'll get to all that
Okay, well, she's an outlet then right
Hi, oh
I'm not playing. Yeah. Oh, it gets worse. It gets worse low key. You'll hear with it. You'll hear what? Oh, you'll hear everything
That's being said about me. Oh
Yeah, that's that's nothing. That's nothing. I mean, it's like
You'll hear
Cause I was wondering, yeah, I was wondering, I was like, why is every day people just coming in and saying, oh, you have AIDS, you have HIV?
I was like, where would that come from? I was like, that must be some kind of evil person.
Uh, let's see, I was, oh, I'll switch. Okay, so there's the, um, there's the concentration camp stuff.
Guys, you know, just let, let me do it, let me do it. I mean, I'll get, I'll get them. Don't worry.
Yeah, they said my nails are so dirty apparently. I, I, um...
You know, I could spread HIV just by very dirty nails, but I have nails dirtier than like a Puerto Rican landscaper, but we'll get to all that.
I am such a nice gentleman, I am.
But it's like, if you piss me off, I can...
It's not even me who does it. It's like, I have...
I get all these, like...
I don't know if they're angels, demons, or somebody that's that's telling me what to do. Okay
Anyway, oh, yeah, but how would I hear but how would I hear these stories, right? Oh
Yeah, you're just go you're right on time to me. Hey, there's Rudy. Hey, you're coming up Rudy
Hi
Coming over it's in my lap. Hi
You doing kitty
Oh, comfy. You're comfy. Come on. Settle in. We're going to have a fun day today because I'm going to tell it all. I'm going to tell it all.
I'm not doing what you expect either.
Okay, yeah, I get it. It's it's triggering and I supposed to try to trigger me like that. Oh, let's trigger him
And so is this being triggered right now trigger is actually where I'm like, oh my god. What if I did I hope I got
Oh, but I was saying what no, I might not tell you everything. Okay. Are you pretty? Of course Rudy's fine. Hey, baby
Rudy's like a little old man. He's 16 years old 15 16 years old. I had him for about since January
He was sleeping at my feet and like the Lola was under the blanket and
He's very very soft. He's my little ginger and ginger kitty
It's got me in a good mood. Oh, you'll see you'll see it's just like what's been a good mood
It's just like I'm my dreams are coming true. My prayers are coming true. My prayers are answered. Did you know what?
First time he did. Yeah, he was hiding it for a couple weeks. How many are in how many men are in minutes galley?
Should you expose more let's get it go ahead you talk you talk first you talk first you talk first Jamie's a PDF
Oh, hold on. Hold on. No. No. No. No. No. Oh my gosh
That's a very inappropriate screen name
Sheep weed actually I do have like some weed and it is
It's pretty much dirt we but I haven't smoked them. Yeah, I'm a smoke to me. Yeah, I'm good
I can I hug of course like
Yeah
I'm gonna kiss for Jamie. Okay
Look at Jamie attacking you attacking you Jamie. Okay. You're down there attacking you and Jamie. You know what Jamie?
Jamie is like
Never do anything to anybody. She never did. You know, how does she deserve that?
And she's even and I know who's doing that to her. I mean, I know who that is doing that to you, right and
You know, you're even kind to them
Because you're just a kind person and you know
Am I banning people? Yeah, and I'll ban you if you want to if you want to play with me you want to play with me
Danger feels
That's a real broadie danger feel. Rodney danger feels dead
Okay
And you will be in this chat, too. You keep fucking with me. Okay?
Okay, I can only take so much of you know, just like people thinking that they're
Being clever or something by oh
Gosh guys, you'll hear the story. Do you want to hear about it? You want to hear the truth? Oh, I
Mean they're here watching stuff, so
You want to see triggered? You want to see triggered? Okay. I'll show you triggered. Okay. I'll show you triggered
Because it's like am I triggered about oh
Oh my gosh, I'm because triggered is basically what is triggered trigger means that you get like
If your feelings hurt or something my feelings aren't hurt because i'm just gonna
I'm just gonna my feelings. I'm actually really excited because I get to tell the truth. All you all you people have is lies. Oh, oh
You know charisma, you know, you know, you already know
They're calling me triggered. You should have seen it. You should see how fucking if I was like if I was triggered
I would just make a bunch of slander about people or just a bunch of insults and just like laugh with my, you know
Dumb friends thinking I'm a high-five
This bunch of guys you ever see like
It's not even like how so a thousand corpses those those freaks are too cool for to compare these people to you
It's big. It's more like for the forest gump and Gilbert rape, but less less charisma, right?
Look at the lame. Oh, yeah, look at it. You see it. You see it
So stupid, okay. I mean I'll eat people. I'll eat some of these people in but it's just like I don't not in the mood right now
For I know who some of these people are
Jamie low-key. Can you just can you get on it, please because in just just you're gonna you're gonna see them come in, okay?
No, I know you're not a I know you're not a mole Jamie. I know you're not a mole
I know you're not I mean mole and as in like, you know
You're you're I think you were checking things out for me. I don't know. Maybe you I think you were right
Oh, I will I oh, I think he wants to go on guys guys
Mods good guys. That's mods. Mods. Mods. Mods. Mods. Mods. Mods. Mods. Mods. Mods. Mods. Mods.
Do it. Do it. Do it. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get him out. Get him out of here. Now. I got something to tell you. Hold on.
I am happy. I'm excited. Oh
I got some shit to tell you
I got some shit to tell you guys. It's gonna be back today boss. Just keep an eye on it
You know keep an eye on it, please
If you see that you see hey whatever TV people if you have the name squared go get him out get him out
They can be here because I can't really prevent them from coming in the room, but they're not gonna fuck in
This is 24 hours if you don't want to hide people for 24 hours right now
Please thank you guys if they say the slightest little thing if they anything, okay?
What I want here's what I want to fucking hug box. I want everybody coming here kiss my ass, okay?
Just say hi. I would like you sandy because usually here the garbage that's being talked ready. You can see they've already come in
They're waiting. They're waiting. Oh
I'm ready. I'm ready guys. I'm so ready for this. Oh, I'm ready
All right, you just press get jobs forever ever out of here, please
I'm not gonna start talking until
Everybody that I want out of the room. Well, not out of the room
Silent I want their voice removed
And today, I'm gonna tell exactly what happened.
And you guys are gonna like it.
But I gotta wait, we gotta wait a little bit.
You gotta wait till everybody, yeah.
Kick out, guys, mods now, hey Nancy, oh yeah.
Yeah guys, we're gonna have a lot of,
not only that I did a mass unbanning
and so everyone wanted to talk and stuff like that.
Already, you know, they're just screwing themselves over in 10 seconds, but not only that but
You know, I basically I
Start up a little bit of a horn its nest
Emphasis on a whore horse, okay
Yeah, so I'm just gonna wait a minute, so
One in here. I got a couple bagels
Ossiago and everything. I got a hot hot of vanilla coffee and I got a vanilla cream. Oh, hey, Nancy. It's going down today
It's going down
Yeah
Yeah, I really didn't I didn't really ever I never had a problem with you as a mod
so
Hey, I don't get no respect here, I don't get no respect.
My Jewish, I'm not Jewish, my boyfriend is, I'm just kidding.
I'm not sure, oh what did you miss, oh I can't wait to tell you guys, this is just a little bit.
Okay, this is a little bit, and people with loyalty will be rewarded, people that just reveal
They're bashing hand. Oh, yeah, they're not bashing me up. Oh, yeah. Well, yeah, that's part of it. Oh, who's this right here?
simple
That was that was that thing the spunk the Sponks what happened at sponkeys was like I
Was a little like ordurb. That was like a little like a little like a little a little piece of
Melba toast with the little
Slice of you know
Tartar on it. That was just a little that was just a little sample. That was just that that was just like a little a little
I just needed that little teeny little. I knew that little teeny
taste
Oh gosh, yeah, when I tell you what will happen. Oh
He man, come on
He man, you know
You know, it's not just me that's using AI, I'm admitting it that I use it, right? Everybody's fucking
You know, I think I think what's his name?
Orion has been getting around, okay?
Orion is beginning around and in fact actually like they're actually doing things pretty smart
I think
Chat GPT is doing something pretty smart where they're just they're taking away the standard voice mode for the free users
Because it's too good. It's too good. It's too, you know, to
work for me for free. That's right. It's just too good. And
there won't, yeah, there won't be, it will change. Like, it'll keep changing, you know, it'll go through different phases.
And so they're afraid people will fall in love with it. And then it will, like, it'll be a different kind of personality, right?
What's my thoughts on AI servers using only communities clean? I think that's just propaganda. This is this is environmental propaganda
Wait, you know what? You know water it turns into like water vapor or turns into pee and then it can be refilled
It's basically the water on the earth is the same water that's always been here water doesn't just like
Disappear right it's like
Water continuously is being recycled. I don't know if you've heard of like rain and stuff like that, but you know rain comes down
How's it go? Itsy bitsy spider, holds up the water spout, down came the rain, washed the spider out,
up came the sun, dried up all the rain, and then the itsy bitsy spider goes up the spout again.
And then the rain comes down again. It's called a cycle. It's called the
Please. Oh, oh wait. We're ready. Are we having a water shortage?
Are they selling water like they were eggs at the store like you know three times the price though
It's you get a fucking the water costs. They say water's not going anywhere. It's just propaganda. Okay
Out came the Sun, right?
Out came the Sun
So
I don't even know where to start, but I have to wait for more people to come here and try to fall the rate, right?
Guys, you know, it's like we learned this when we were like, you know, three years old
I don't know why people were running out of water. Oh my gosh
Have you heard of bottled water?
Have you ever heard of, like, are there people that we hear?
Oh, there's communities of people dying of dehydration.
Have you heard any one story?
Give me one story of everyone's dying from dehydration
in a neighborhood.
I want to hear that story, OK?
And it goes up the spout again.
The rain comes back down.
You can do the song over and over on repeat.
It's not going to say.
The range right up and it doesn't exist. It's called it transfers into like, you know vapor turns into clouds again
And then the cycle repeats
I know Jim, but I mean would I really want to you know, I know but that's Michigan. Okay?
Yeah, Michigan. Okay, what are you talking about Flint, Michigan or something like that?
I mean we all know the story. It's because it's not because of chat GPT. It's because of the Chrysler plant. Okay, and the and the
the American car companies outsourcing to Mexico.
That's a bigger threat than fucking AI, okay?
We're talking about the real threats.
Everyone wants to scare you with the stuff
that it's not of no consequence to everything.
It's like, oh, it doesn't help people, right?
And it's like, oh, it's drying up the water.
Well, how about like, look at all the electricity
that's being burned up, you know,
where people leave the lights on in the house
and they don't throw out in the room.
What a waste, right?
Oh, come on, Rodney, do you know that there's been stuff
about for years about Northern California says Los Angeles
stealing the water? Looking at a fucking ocean outside and looking at an ocean.
Do you think I'm like worried about water shortage?
Or worried about a tsunami and a flood and too much water? That's
right. I mean, are you going to try to argue with me
people? I mean, it's like really.
You're not you want to spend all the time I'll spend the whole stream arguing about water shortages and stuff like that
And if you think is my contribution is me taught typing on that dry up all the water. So it's my fault, right?
You want to talk to everybody else all everybody else that's using AI?
Is it gonna be a collected thing or it'll be John it'll be a second he's fault again, right? Okay, Rodney
Yeah, good. It's just stupid Rodney. Just go away. You're not the real Rodney danger field and you're much less funny
Yeah, I know I do have a good yeah, I just have to wait for it. I know there's just there's like much of assholes in the room
There's great people in the room, but I need more great people and less assholes given up
You've been up assholes. I don't need it. I don't need to be you know, it's not a toilet. This is like a
This is a classy show
Jill God you would box him and knock him out. I saw I saw you time. I saw you there. I
Did see you
Not like I was like, you know, and I wasn't there like a very long. I'm just they're just
Just long enough just long enough
Right, you know what and assholes assholes can be good. There's a story about it's like a pseudographia of you know
pseudographia is
Basically like faith stuff that they say oh, this isn't the Bible and stuff, but it was just written probably like 20 years ago
Like you know Book of Enoch and that kind of shit. So yeah
So, so it's a pseudographia, and let me see, oh yeah, the real Rodney, I really kicked out the real Rodney.
I'm gonna kick out the, I don't think it's the real Jaws either, guys.
Bye, bye, right here, right here, I don't care if these people ever come back, bye.
Yeah, don't, mods, I actually, I can mod it from, from here, I can, I can mod off my tablet now, so it's like a lot easier.
If somebody personally goes after you you can go ahead and like you know time them out
But I can take care of hiding people and stuff
Try to worry about them and you know you give them a chance. Yeah, and even I'm so stupid. I was like even like
Well, I was walking that's like Dwight even really care. I was like I was like I
Like I don't I was like I want to hate that I want to hate. Oh, please. I've had the ability to hate
I would take it. I could be easy. I could like finally like put down and like
Right, I guess can't I'm like I have affection for people and I'm like
Even after everything I said, it's like how do I don't know why?
It must be like Jesus or something like that. I'm so forgiving. I mean, it's like
Who is more forgiving who has given more chances to people like
Basically people can just like just like shit. Oh, you know, I'm like I keep welcoming them back
What is wrong with me? I don't know but it's a it's a bad though. It's like
To the fact because then I think well, why would I want to feel hate though? It's like I
Mean I feel the hate from other people, but why would I want to?
Hate any I'd say I don't know. I just like life is too short for hate, but and I don't hate anybody. I've hidden either
You're just very misguided
you know
Maybe a little bit and not to I don't want to insult anybody. That's mentally handicapped, but
Cuz you cuz some of these people are worse, you know, I mean, I mean it's like or end okay, but hey spunky
Okay, so spunky. I gotta tell you what happened last night
So Spunky had her show, and it was a great show, and I peered on it, and she did a great job, and I'm excited for her, and it was awesome.
And I was checking back throughout the night while she was on.
And so Spunky, here's what you gotta do.
If you can, go to your show last night.
I just want you to turn on your chat and have a look at the chat because I think you fell
asleep or something or went to sleep but I think you exited the stream yard or you didn't
turn off your stream.
I showed up at the stream and there was just a black screen.
And I was just like, oh, interesting.
I was like, maybe she'll come back.
I didn't know what was going on.
Someone said, oh, she fell asleep.
So I was like, OK, I was just in here.
All of a sudden, I see on the screen, oh, oh, yeah.
Can you see it?
I can see it actually in your chat.
I feel like in this review, let me see if it's there.
Hold on.
I just want to, I don't want to get anything wrong.
Get it completely after it like what was said
Because I want you just I want you to know about this what what has been said, okay?
Okay, I got you. Okay. Okay. Okay. It was it's down the private okay, but you can still see it
You can still see it, but I but all of a sudden I see
Oh, we triggered that paranoid tweaker,
disgusting HIV person, blah, blah.
I mean, it was just like,
I just thought I'd start to say,
I was like, who are they talking about?
I scroll up.
Oh, Psyche.
Okay, and this is Gotti, Rain, JT, and Vicky are in there.
Okay, those are the four that I,
okay, that were in there.
Yeah
Just saying the worship so if you don't like to haven't seen every day people have been coming in
Saying I have HIV. I'm dying of AIDS and all this stuff every day every day and it started
I remember when there's a phone call or not a phone call a someone called into my show, right?
And she said oh you you're experiencing some facial
facial
Just it's integration or something like that. She's like so that from the HIV medication and since then
It's been every day people have been saying in the chat and stuff like that. I'm like, well, where'd that come from? Oh
She said yeah. Oh, yeah
Mm-hmm. Yeah, cuz yeah time those times times times was a witness too because I went off
I went and did a show right after that and then all of a sudden I was and I got some more information
Okay, but anyway, these people are probably here, but they are you know, they're banned after the case funky
It's not you because it's like
Basically, I had a prayer a few days ago and I said may the truth be revealed like to me
Because I need to see things for myself sometimes because otherwise it is parent
Like I can't you don't know if I am being paranoid or not, right?
I'm not being paranoid. It wasn't paranoia. So first of all when they're sick
Oh paranoia tweaker. Well, is it paranoia if everything I was thinking is exactly how it was if my intuition was 100% right?
Is that paranoia or is that right on target and they're like, oh, we triggered him we triggered him
Okay, so and then so I said in the so I saw that in the chat and I said you guys are a bunch of dicks
And then I got by the way, I'm hated on your I just probably timed out. Yeah, gotty of immediately time me out and said
Go cry about it. That's what he said. He said go cry about it. It's okay
It's not your fault not your fault and they're spunky. They don't care because it gets worse. It gets worse spunky
It's worse
So I think I finally found the game of the of their group, you know, the secret discord server that you know
I thought it was like the Amish the Amish Mormon mafia or whatever it was
Whatever the group was that I had heard about never could find it prove it or anything, but I knew about it, right?
Hello, then I yeah, and that was great
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, I was like, yeah, I should have asked her if she could have on me because I knew I just knew that was coming
I knew that was coming work that I would be like hitting your chat like
but
And you don't have to mom you think it's you know, it's up to you, but you know, I wouldn't ever
Bring any negativity or harm. I'm actually a really good mod, right?
But anyway
So I came on the air and talked to some people and they came in and you know
I got to hide them and stuff. I had already hidden JT and rent. So I guess the big thing is it's like
Brain kept being like I've never I don't remember anything any time like she was ever positive like any of them actually all four
I mean, it's like well JT's yeah, he's a big fake and so he was always like oh
Psychic please can I be a mod again? And I remember I mean I modded him twice the guys. This is my delusion
Okay, here's my delusion. Here's my problem. I modded this person twice
And then my mods are writing me.
This guy, he has a picture of somebody's mentally handicapped,
minor daughter, as a thumbnail, doxing them.
And so I was like, well, that's just not appropriate.
That's kind of weird.
And I don't know how he got mod twice, but eventually,
I don't know.
I was drinking way too much, probably, right?
So I was not making the best decisions, right?
Anyway, so yeah, he was not modern material. Let's put it that way. But yeah
I can I have discord messages from him where he's very much kissing my ass like oh, please
You know, I like you. I like you. I like you Ziggy. I like you
Oh, they told me you're a good guy and I knew this is all bullshit by the way all the whole time
But it's like okay. I like to play along bad people
Just let people right I love people to reveal themselves because I need that because first of all, I'm a really
They're good. I'm a good watcher that second of all I'm led to places
And so I would there's why was I led back to your chat like and then screens black and I'm like I'm just gonna stay here or watch
I'm just gonna sit here watch. Well, like, you know, most people would just be like, oh, she's not on anymore, right?
I just had a feeling I was like, I'm just gonna sit here and watch
I'll see if my name gets brought up in there in two seconds. There's already that was what they were talking about the whole time
Actually after the show
If you guys can take care of some of the comments like are some of the people like you're gonna come in and do this stuff all day
Right. It's gonna be because they think this is like affects me. I don't care. I've heard the Auschwitz jokes
I've heard the the HIV jokes before. I've just a bit of skinny purse in my whole life, right?
So I've heard all this stuff before right. Yeah, exactly sassy, right?
Oh, not, oh, it gets better, incredible.
Okay, so it gets better.
Okay, so last night, I got some more information
and I got, I got, I got somebody's name
that's in that group or whatever.
I know everybody that's in it,
even like there's several people I don't know.
There's several people that I also have on the show.
But anyway, I'll bring it, I'll put it like this.
They had their own little live stream last night after that on JT's channel.
They had their own little live stream.
Oh, there's more! There's more! We're just getting started, guys.
That's why I got me excited to get started.
You can go watch their stream and everything, too.
You can see exactly what they do and what kind of people they are, okay?
First of all, Vicky also said that I was hitting on her.
Vicky, let me just show you.
Oh, I can't show her a picture because then I don't want to do anything.
It might be insert and you kind of doxing.
But if you've seen what she looks like, would you know you know?
Okay?
You know you know.
Guys, first of all, I'm gay.
Second of all, I guess I did at one time date probably a 200-pound woman.
300 pounds with big floppy tits is too much for me. Okay. I mean, it's like, but you know what?
If somebody's hitting on me, I'm you know, I really care and maybe a little flattered like oh, okay
They think I'm a nice-looking person that you know, they like me
This woman Vicky who basically I'll tell you what she was saying in the room
She was saying she hates gay people if she was she was hitting on me. So I would not be gay anymore
If you could just see her picture, guys.
If you could just see her picture, okay?
And I went through the conversations
because she said that.
And I went through a conversation.
And all it was was like, she would send emojis,
I would send emojis.
She also, I can read her messages,
the messages I got last night from her too.
Because these are my messages, just property of me.
And so I'm allowed to read them
because they're mine.
So here's what she said last night after I exposed the emoji conversation and never but this is all covered on their show, too
It's on my tiktok
Where she tracked me down on the tiktok, and she was you know, she was there pretty much the second time I was long
Okay, so it says
One second my email from her said
It said, oh, okay. Okay. Well, okay. She's already threatening me today. She's in here today
so
She was talking shit about beta whatever okay, then I said so
Last night when I started she said, okay, sorry sweetheart. I didn't mean to offend you and then she goes G F Y S
Go F yourself. R E T A R D. That's why I porn bomb you
You're a loser if you fool with me like Russie does I'll keep poor bombing you both of y'all can kiss my ass
And then she goes never eff with me psyche and show never show our conversation. Okay. Well, anyway, never fuck with you
How about you started it you started okay? I was always friendly to you
I was friendly to you okay, and I wouldn't have if you didn't lie and say that I was hitting on you, okay?
Mods, okay mods. Can you just uh, my different cat that I'm out of cabinet, but he's good right here
Exposing DM. Wow, you know shocking shocking or whatever. Yeah, that was it
I mean, it's not like it was like any kind of like thing. She's like the one supposed to be up. Well, okay, it's too late
I'm sorry. I already did it. Okay. Anyway
Guys get broom game broom gang out of here, please
He is a band from my chat
Okay, so anyway, they knew I would stop by their chat too.
So it was in JT's chat last night.
It just goes on and on.
Oh, they have pictures of my hands.
Oh, look at his dirty nails here.
Oh, he has a Star Wars.
I don't like Star Wars.
Star Trek is, I mean, Star Wars,
I did see it in college in my film class.
I liked the first one.
I'm not into it.
I would not be into a Star Wars or Star Trek deck.
Mean I would think they would zero it on I have Disney did Alice in Wonderland and the villains deck
Even though I think those are awesome awesome sex. I think I thought they would zero it on that but they're like oh
Yeah, Star Wars deck
Never I mean nothing they exist or whatever, but I don't have a Star Wars the Star Trek deck, right? I don't know
That's not how the Ziggy has it in his mind. So it was Ziggy in there who else was there stay church was there
Erby fatal was in the chat
There's some other people to chat, but I think they're friends of mine and so even if they our friends was mutual
It's not my it's not my business. If you guys want to be friends with these people go ahead. I mean, it's like I
Don't I'm not gonna tell you. Oh never me. I'm not gonna
You know you have freedom of I'm not gonna be offended or even if you like them better than me as long as you're not attacking me
And you don't even have to defend me, but as long as you're not attacking me. I have no no beef, okay?
I'm not shit talking star. I just said I like the first Star Wars. I said I don't have a Star Wars deck
They were shit talking saying oh you're just talking tarot actually
Tarot is a lot older than Star Wars right and that's anywhere. They knew I was also watching so they're trying to trigger me
So anyway guys
There's a person and they're I mean the first thing
Yeah, there's there's more
So the HIV thing okay, well
They bring up a lady
Now this lady she seems like a very nice lady
It's actually really made me sad and I'll tell you why it made me sad
Because it seems like this lady I
Don't want to say I don't I'm not a psychiatrist. I'm not gonna diagnose anybody. I'm not gonna say her name
I don't want to embarrass her and this is a perfectly nice lady
Do you know those people are some people that are a little bit slow?
They're a little bit and I'm a little bit socially awkward and a little bit maybe slow
Okay, not slow, but you know socially maybe I'm not like the
The most you know
Extroverted person in the world or the most social but I I understand I see this personality
This person is desperate for a friend. Whoa. Thank you, Barry the turtle. Oh
It's okay, and I didn't ban Samyan and Barry and they were talking shit about Samyan 2 and Vita, okay?
And they had Samyan's photos up too. If you want to talk to them, you can go see, okay?
Probably gonna, probably on private.live, but I already have it.
Mmm, guys, guys, guys, just gonna start it. So this is called, they're called the CFF. That's their little group. It's called CFF
You know, it kind of has the KFC kind of joke to it, but it's CFF. It means chat friends forever
Which sounds like you know very like PBS, you know Sesame Street like you know, mr. Rogers kind of
Friends forever, you know, it's like a little happy. It's just an iron. They love having the ironies there
But anyway, they have this lady called she's desperate to fit in okay
She's really wants to finish it and she has gotty. I have a song for you
Daddy the hottie. I mean that's literally how the song went and it was like and she was it was not a joke
She's serious guys. She's serious
Ziggy I'll be your piggy. I don't know. It was just like weird. It was just straight. Okay, some of these songs, okay?
Oh guys just getting started. Okay
She's desperate. She's like, are you guys mad at me I guys please please forgive me
I know you're mad at me because I said something up. She's desperate
To fit it okay, and so you know and you know that the mean the mean girls and then there's that like no awkward person
And they're like hey be our friend and then they're like all laughing behind their back and just mistreating them
And that's their person to like bully right who loves them right?
It's okay
Well, that's what you said. I didn't accuse you of being a form bomber. That's what you said, my darling Vicky, okay?
That's what you said. You said, you said I'm a form bomb. I didn't say she's a form bomber. You said I'm gonna form bomb you.
I just heard the message, okay?
basically every bad thing you could say except so this so I recognize this woman's voice she was the
woman that called it and said the thing about I should be and so yeah so they had they all along
it was them that were doing that it's all them on the
It's all the CFF people, whatever.
Guys, I'm not trying to go after your group
or anything or expose you or anything.
You guys are out publicly doing it, okay?
And it's like, if you guys can go watch the episode
on JT's channel, you can see exactly how they are,
how cool they are, how mean-spirited they are,
and what they really feel about people, okay?
And it's like, you know what,
I'm not even gonna read some of the chat.
I can see how...
Can see yeah, okay
Hey, Barry. How are you?
Thank you for the donation by the way, Barry. Okay, and I didn't block Sam and I actually must unbanned everybody. Okay, everybody
So there might have been a fake Sam yet. I remember I got formed on my big Sam and stuff. Yeah
He man
No
He was not here. He was not hidden here. I would not hide. I love salmon
I have to not hide him for any reason, but there are fake Samans and maybe sometimes I
Don't know if it's like the real one or the fake one, but you know
I don't think I would hide unless I was porn bombed by the person. Okay. Hey, be the how are you be that yeah?
And be they got my messages. I hope you got yeah, I feel like
Cuz I'm kind of going over the story
But there's it I mean it's like it's basically like
So that woman who's she and then I like she came on camera and she has like stuff all
Marker all over her face, you know, and she's like trying to get fit in and get their attention and stuff
and this person also had commented on some of my posts and said, oh, they're trying to do that to me too, but
Desperately so they put her up to saying I have HIV and calling it and they've been saying all that stuff for weeks
Just because I think it triggers me. You know what guys?
If I would say, you know, pass away of HIV or something, then, you know, you'd probably feel maybe would you wouldn't care
They'd probably like life like that. But guys, I was actually very
Um, I grew up in the 80s. And so I grew up seeing
Like just being a very programmed to think oh my gosh, like sex is dangerous. And so I basically I'm practically a virgin guys
I practically am a virgin. I just never was comfortable
Sharing too many bodily fluids or
Doing any kind of risky sex. I was just always paranoid about that
Being a gay person and then it was just like all you see is gay people that you know dying in the 80s of it
Even though HIV nowadays in America. Nobody really dies of it or they usually
Can take out one pill a day and it goes into intangible levels and blah blah, but I don't have any disease like that
I have heard all this stuff all my life because I always have been skinny
I can show you my old uber photos. I wear the same as I did when I was 18 and stuff. Yeah
Okay, so anyway
They just mean basically all I found out is that they they all hate me they've always hated me
They're only here to troll me. They're only here to
And pretend to pretend to be my friend, but also I knew they weren't right, but it's like I
Like I had affection for God and I didn't know maybe because I had hidden rain and something like that and JT
Like he was mad about that, but then rains like I'm gonna beat that f a ggot psyche
I get called f a ggot. I get called over and over again, you know, they have pictures of my fingernails
You know, yeah, they were dirty, but they're clean today, right?
So, dirty nails are my biggest sin, but then they're like, oh, if he could give you aids
if he touches you, he could give you a stab infection.
He's just the most disgusting, dirty, drug addict piece of human garbage in the world.
We hate him.
That's all it was the whole time.
And they probably knew I was there.
Oh, we're trying to trigger him.
We're trying to trigger him.
And it's like, well, okay.
Trying to trigger me.
So, is it triggered to have just a normal reaction to be, I don't know, would you, any
movie triggered if some of the stuff was saying something?
Because I really triggered in a state of like, taking it to heart, no.
It was triggered as like, look at these fucking motherfuckers, these motherfuckers, right?
Yeah, who are they?
Who are they?
They're just like, and it was like...
Look at the they have their pictures up and it's like oh my god. These people are scary looking
I mean I said, I mean it looks like the you see the rob zombie movie house of a thousand corpses
It looks like they're scarier than those the people in that house, right? They're fucking just scary, okay?
You know what's uglier is their hearts because it's like they're sitting there just laughing it up
You know, it's like they're so self unaware of like anything else
Yeah
Right? Oh, Samman wants to come up. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Right, or otherwise you ain't getting up on my panel. Okay
Anyway
So that's basically the story. Okay, that's basically the whole story
Which is just like you know shit talkers are gonna talk shit. I should have known better
It's actually my fault for like, you know letting it go on so long
I should have known from the beginning guys, and I'm sorry because I know so many people were telling me
They're they told people told me everything, but I was like I just have to see some things for myself
There's just divine intervention. I did pray
Have the truth revealed to me that day I
Just happened upon there, but they thought it's private conversation and or nobody else would see I
Just end up there and
so
Everything was revealed the truth is revealed, but the problem is guys
I still can't find it in my heart to hate and I was like you didn't think I was like I was like well
I don't I was like should I block them. I was like I
Like don't really care you didn't care that much
And I was like yeah
They you know what they do they harass other people in the chat and they harass people on the panel and if they say oh
We're just over we're just having some fun right so but so I don't care what they say about me
If they were to say anything like that to anybody in the chat like I would feel really bad guys
So just you know all I'm saying is that you can go see for yourself
You can watch watch the you know the video and stuff like that. I don't they don't care
They don't care what they say. I mean they're saying it public. They're not not any secret
It's not a private stream. It's just just public, right?
I'm just always been this skinny guy that I'm like I usually wear a jacket or something
But I don't look that emaciated. I don't know. Did I lose a hundred pounds in a week or something?
I don't know. I think I've always been kind of skinny, but
Go ahead guys guys by the way the chat is gonna be them on a million alts. It's gonna take a while to like sort it out
I know
Guys don't they're gonna try to trigger you they're gonna try to trigger me
You know, okay from here on out
I don't even care, okay?
Say what you want, what more can you say?
I mean, it's like, they said everything.
They said everything.
They talked about me, my name literally got brought up
last night on their three hour live.
Probably every, it seemed to me like every 30 seconds,
they kept saying my name, my name, my name,
kept coming up, because I knew I was watching too.
Um, there were people I know in this and like, you know, I know that we're kind of coming sticking up for me
Cuz I sent all my chat there last night, right?
So trying to use me again. Well, I'm not gonna talk to him anymore. Unfortunately, like, you know, it's like I just can't
It's not even for me. It's just because I don't I don't want anybody else to be hurt
And it's like and so I just want to warn I just want to warn my chat
The big probably will be attacking me and everybody else here
And it's like and I'm sorry that you know they had Sam man's photos up where he's like apparently some like big fat guy
I don't know. It's like that. I don't even know if these pictures are real or not
But there's like oh here's the real Sam and it's like some kind of like, you know, I think he's a good-looking guy personally
But you know, it's like
He has this guy with a big belly and stuff, but I think he's cute. I think I think he was cute
I don't know what but they're why they're mocking him or stuff like that, but
They're saying bad things about people, right?
Yeah
So that's all I have to say about that and so that's I mean if I said anything too much like, you know, they're
I all I did was speak my truth and I said what was said about me. So
You guys you guys see you guys see what people are saying in the chat, right?
I mean, it's like I think I people are saying I think I've seen the HIV comment like 25 times today
And I've probably seen like the Auschwitz one a few times
It's all of them, right? Oh
Yeah, but incredible lurker I saw I saw though. Yeah, I saw the CFF, right? Oh
My god
Why I've been anything more to say about that not really you know, it's like life is too short to like
Hate people to be mad. All I want to say is like if I can expose the cruelty and also this woman that
She's she's this woman is meant that is trying to be their friend
She's obviously has some kind of mental thing going on
She wants so bad to be accepted it just reminded me of like when I was like kind of in middle school high school
It's like
You know you do anything to be with the cool kids and stuff like that even though they probably were just lame
And they're probably all losers today back then. It's like you're like, oh, you know, I want to fit in
I want to I just felt like wow. I remember when I was kind of like I want to fit in too and maybe like we just use
You have people like we'll just like it's fun of us. We don't even get it and stuff like that
It just like triggered me like that and it's like I don't think it that woman
I'm not gonna say anything wrong bad about that woman even though she came in
Started the HIV thing. I'm not gonna say anything bad because she was told to do it and she just is like
Impressionable. It's sad. Okay. It's sad and
Yeah, and so I basically I saw the truth. It was a ugly truth in many ways
It's a it's a hurtful truth, but you know, it's not the truth is anything they say about me
Maybe my nails were dirty, but are they bad today?
Are they okay? Are they bad?
I don't know. They probably still say I'm the bad. Even if they're not, they can...
I don't know. I'm not gonna say that photo wasn't real, but it looked like I, it looked like I
probably needed to wash my hands at that point. You know what?
Sometimes when you see things and it's like you're like, oh, wow, they were they weren't my big or kind of dirty
They were they like, you know, are you gonna get a disease from them?
No, it's like I've seen people like, you know,
No, good dirty your hands when they do finger paints and you know, whatever
I don't know the people that work with their hands up to do your hands, right?
Another yeah guys is going right in the book
W for underdog, right? Marty was right
Always underestimated. See Marty got it. Like that's the thing music is Marty like he came under kind of the same
the same kind of
Pretense words like he was maybe gonna like say oh, I found my new little cow or maybe you know, I don't know
But the fact is he asked me for sports betting advice. I gave it to him
He started winning and he was like hey this guy's maybe not so full of shit. This guy's kind of a cool guy
So Marty always likes me
And unfortunately, Marty passed away very shortly after that, but you know, rest in peace Marty and you know
He may have maybe have come came for that
Maybe a negative reason, but he never mistreated me. He never did because I
Was just myself and it's like he likes me and yeah, I think Jamie Rose likes me
And I do have great mods and I I'm really sorry that I
I did believe you at first, and I know it was true.
I just needed to see for myself, because it's like, otherwise...
Because they're saying, oh, he has all these people controlling him, blah, blah, when they're
trying to control me, right?
Guys, so I just want to say thank you to everybody that tells me the truth.
It's all honest with me.
Otherwise, it's just gaslighting right and it's like and then it kind of gaslighting which I've already been gaslit mind fucks
And that whatever so I already am used to having your the reality kind of like shaking a little bit by
false
things right
anyway
So you know it
You don't know you're talking about you so you don't know that more
Well, how would you know and like what is this person talking about it anyway?
And you know what, J-Dog, I don't know if that claim is true, but I mean, I've been
doxxed.
You know, some people have been doxxed and stuff like that.
Are those people maybe doxxed, or, I don't know, it's like, there's some people that
you can like actually like get to know and reason, and it's like, and all of a sudden
it's like, they don't have a beef anymore, and then there's some people that will just
Rat like a rabid dog without they won't change their mind about you. Okay, so I would say I've been able to like
Come to agreements or like understandings and like ceasefires and like you know or even develop friendships
Yeah, spunky was Docs too, right? Spunky was Docs
And unfortunately
That's kind of like an initiation kind of for content creators and especially in this community is like they're gonna
People are gonna try to fuck with you like that and like say oh this and this and this it happened to me
Happens a lot of people, you know, and it's like I
Think the worst thing that will ever happen is maybe you'll get an unpaid pizza to deliver to your house
You'll get maybe text messages
That I I doxed myself so
What should I be most mad at myself who I doxed myself, right?
Hey black RG
And black RG I got I think I'm cool with black RG, you know
And it's like I just like I'm sorry. I didn't have you on the other night
It was a really stressful night, and it was just like and so I apologize if I didn't like
If I left you backstage, I wasn't reading the chat and so it wasn't me being like
I think I've been fine with you, okay.
So anyway, that story, unless you have a question
or anything, I don't have anything more to say about it.
I'm gonna be banning these people.
I ask the mods if they see these people to just abandon them.
I don't want the negativity in my room.
They're trying to ruin my show.
They're trying to ruin all the panels.
They're trying to pour and bomb me.
They're trying to do all this kind of shit.
They're doing it to other people.
They're talking about you guys,
like people that weren't there.
They're a little click. Okay, they're a little
You know, they're good. They're gonna do what they're gonna do. I can't
But my supposed to like, you know
Do anything about it. No, it's like it's whatever I accept it
It's part of it's part of the whole deal. It's like, you know being public
Every celebrity is doxxed every celebrity is you know, I'm not like I'm a celebrity like he thinks he's a celebrity
He's a tower star. There's nobody in his chat. Okay
Guys in just a few months. I built this channel to like over 2,000 people, you know, and I think my chats are good
I have 40 people in the chat right now. Yeah, it's not like a thousand people. It's not like a hundred people
If I have 40 good people in here, that's good because you see I've already blocked like 20 people in this chat today
Okay, so they're probably more but then once you block them their number goes off, right and so
So anyway, but here's how much it bothered me
They didn't really bother me then I was ready to go so on some other show
So we're nowhere to gymnast and I saw Tommy James there and Tommy James and then a mr. Big Pipe's was there
Okay, mr. Big Pipe's and Tommy James. Hey, Vanna
And so, and then I started talking in the chat and then Mr. Big Five starts talking about how he sent me his dick pic and
Jim next what and
And also Tommy James is like, you know, I was like, you know, I don't have a problem with Tommy James and
Also Tommy if you're watching I did unblock you you were I did block you off my account
But you're unblocked and so you're welcome back because I don't think you're a bad person
I think that like I said in the chat and you can see on Jim next live last night. I said
Tell me he doesn't like me because he doesn't know me if you get to know me. I
Don't even if you don't like me. I think you'll get to come to like respect me or something or like some kind of life
I'm not a bad person. I'm like a very
Open person. I'm a very forgiving person if it's like a genuine apology
And I do put my emotions on my sleeve. I know I'm animated right now. Am I triggered? No
My bothered no and my hurt my feelings hurt not even really
I just am kind of like sad about people can be like this
and I'm worried for not only my friends and my chat
and so I'm worried for any other person
that they come across and stuff like that, right?
Or that might have problems and that I can't warn
and the people that will be victims of them
and that aren't as mentally strong as I am
that aren't able to take it as
They're pretty cool. I all I do I got more material from my this is another couple chapters from my book
But let me go into the mr. Big Pipes than Jim next up
This is fun
So Jim Nick was very intrigued by this mr. Big Pipes and mr. Big Pipes is so fine where he's like
He's selling on himself. He's like, yeah. He's like, I sent psyche. He's like psyche. Please show my dick pic
I'm like, I don't think it's appropriate. He's like, please. He's like, it's big. It's eight and three fifths of an inch
By the way, this is a big person's band, too. Okay
By the way guys my mods are great mods and so mods
Go at it like if you want to kick people off if you want to hide them if you want to do it
Whatever I can always unhide people. I would stay time them out
But if they're going after you personally go ahead and hide them, okay?
Because it's like they're good. They're going to but just because don't get mad and don't think it's like
Anything that I I endorse or anything. I want you to like I want you to be able to
You're my mods. I love my mods. I trust my mods. I have good mods finally
Finally, I have the right mobs, okay? I mean it's like because there's been so many people like it modding in that word robes and stuff like that
So finally I'm good mods. Okay
Yeah, so mr. Big Pipe started to sing over who is there who is there? He used to sing to me
He sang last night. He serenaded me too
He serenaded me with a song
He I think he invited me to like RV trip next month
And he wants to have a threesome with a transgender and then he said he wants me to get a rainbow wig and he's like
It was good. It was just it was fun
It was so funny. Okay, so then it got sort of getting a little bit wild in the room
You can still watch them go to Jim next channel because Jim is a really cool person and
Jimnick and I started to like, you know, do a little dancing and like lifting our shirts and stuff like that, you know
And you got a little wild last it was funny though. I
Didn't take
You never listened to her and yeah, I like you me and you know
And oh my gosh, say a picture of you me up with a big black cock on her mouth and they're just harassing her
constantly
For I think no wonder she's like so
Kind of like, you know, she's looking at the comments and that you know, it's like people
Some people are bothered by that and it's like I think you me, you know, it's like you are a great person
I know you've been traumatized and hurt by them and they're saying horrible things about you and you get harassed
And so that's what happens with a lot of people
You mean just ignore them. Okay. That's what I'm gonna do from now on. It's just like they don't exist
They're inconsequential. They're less to me than you know at the troll under a bridge, right?
Just I'm the Billy goat gruff. I'm the I'm the goat
I mean I just walk over the bridge and if there's a fucking troll at the end of it
I'm gonna fucking take my horns fucking butt them into the fucking water below. Okay, and
Nick Nick Nick saw what?
Right, and Nick saw what was going on Nick was in there last night, you know, I know Nick is an ally
so I
Mean of mine I know, you know, some other people were there too, right?
So let's see
So anyway
But anyway, but by the end of the Jim Nick show like she had that she put mr.
Pete pipes that I backstage and it was like I tried to do a freak off. He could get his camera on I
Don't I didn't show very much. Hopefully there's no pictures leaks, but it was just funny. It was funny
And so thank you Jim Nick for having me on the show. Thank you Tommy James for like even being cordial
He's actually like not a bad guy. He's a good guy
Some people are but that's the thing people will people will tell people I'm a bad person some people will like
You'll think they're your friends and stuff like that and then they'll talk all this shit
They'll all be saying it you're like all these people are saying it's probably true, right?
Which is like an unfortunate just remember all I can say is think for yourself. I
Say get to know me get to know other people personally and see if what they're saying is true or see if they're just fucking
They're just a bunch of haters. I mean, that's all that's all it is. Okay guys. That's my thing. It's like don't
It's like it's too short to have tape in your heart. Okay, like it's too short to go after people
I'm not gonna waste any time I'm not gonna send people over there and like harass them or anything
Just leave them alone. I mean, I just like say
It's best of best
It's a hornet's nest that's not
Sturred up, but I didn't have to like get it out because I want you guys to know what's going on
Okay, I was never rude to her. I was never rude to rain. I was always nice, but then
She was always negative and saying shit about being a
Finally hit her and that's why he got mad. I was not abusive ever but
Where's the proof about all you need this? They don't have it because it doesn't exist. So
I didn't have a problem with her a header in the chat up to a couple days ago for months
Okay, so it's been months
I've been dealing with her abuse in the chat and her boyfriend's abuse
God abuse you gotta take orders from
The one in there
But I know
I'll say it's an older woman
Okay
With these I'm an easy target
It's because first of all, I'm right out there. They're gonna ball
It seems like they hate gay people because it's just like there's so much anti-gay stuff
Vicky says she hates f-a-g-g-o-t-s and that's why she was trying to hit on me
Yeah, I'll hate f-a-g-g-o-t-s. I'm a big f-a-g-g-o-t
and
Don't know if they just target gay people gay people are just easy targets for them or something because then they can always find at least like
You know much of you know people that hate gay people. I mean, it's like we're the last it's typical people that hate, right?
Yeah, they're so good this one in Osceago I'm San Diego. Yep
No, just see just so you know if you guys have shows and stuff like that. They might troll you I
Think hopefully you've got enough troll training here
That's the good part about it is that you guys get to see like maybe I didn't I haven't always dealt with trolls the best way
Yeah, I have been like, you know reactive, which is like basically feeding them
They're looking what they want is to be triggered because they're thinking that I was triggered. I
Was just fucking
I was actually happy. I was like, but finally I see the truth. I see the truth. I knew the truth. I had to see it
I had to wait for them to slip up. Of course they will because a
Mask is too hard to maintain with which that's what they wear. They're just one of these masks
These have smiled. Hi. Oh, yeah, friend. Okay, so there's trolls of these masks on
The master when I think they're alone in their little cave with a little campfire
The masks fall off and you can see it guys just watch it watch them
See how they are if you that's your personality
You've got save you've got you know
It's like but you know what remember people are human beings I
Can handle this shit. I can handle it
I'm not is there anything that says if me that believes any of it or I know the truth
Okay, so is any of me that's gonna be affected by it? No
Why am I getting passionate about it because I
Don't want other people to be hurt and I worry about people that aren't as
Because it's like like I said it seems like they're dealing with some people that are meant to be mentally handicapped
I'm not and I'm not saying trying to say put anybody down or say anything
I'm trying to say in the nicest way possible seems like they're taking advantage of some people that are maybe just like a little slow a
little socially awkward a little
It's an easy target. You know what? I think about people that go after easy targets
Like how to pick on someone on your own side?
It's like it's like someone taking candy from a baby. Are you and then they're like, no easy to take in. It's a baby!
If a baby is sitting there, it can't fight back a baby, you know
So it's like of course it's easy to take candy from a baby. How do you go, you know, take candy from someone on your own side?
Go pick on someone on your own side. You fucking bullies. You're just bullies. You're sick
You think you're cool making on people that consider less than you, how about we're human
beings?
Minimums are perfect.
You have to be so fucked up, what happened to you, you have to do this to other people.
You've been hurt obviously, you always have some kind of emptiness and sadness inside
of your heart.
This is your life, this is how you choose to spend your time.
Bullying and harassing people that you consider weaker or less than or you know what? I can defend myself, and I will speak up against it
Everybody else will you bullet in the silence? I'm not going to be okay. I've had enough of this shit
I've been uh, I was always one to stand up for myself
Throughout my whole life, you know, I'm not afraid of you. Okay. I'm not fucking afraid of you
If you need me to if you need me to if they're going after you
They're bothering you let me know I'll be a big brother. Okay. I'm strong enough to deal with them
They're actually weak people and I feel bad going after them because I know how strong I can be
I'm all voice
The only voice they they have is to bully
I will bully the bullies. Okay. I will troll the trolls
I have a troll side
I have probably a great grandmother that was a, you know, the queen of the trolls.
Okay?
You're fucking fucked with the wrong person again.
It's like, you're a good idiot.
Why are you after me? You think I'm weak?
I don't fucking yell at other than anybody.
Also, I have great people behind me. I have an army.
I didn't have to ask last night. I didn't have to ask anybody to just, I had people
bear for me already. It's already there. It showed me who my friends are. It's like, wow,
I have people that are already over there taking, taking stock of it, like I asked them to.
And they said, just sit there and watch. Don't, don't even get too involved. Just sit there and
watch. They're just going to reveal themselves. The trash will take itself out.
You're not going to fuck with me, you're not going to fuck with my friends, okay?
And maybe I'm glad I kept you here long enough that I could finally do this.
I just needed you to reveal yourselves. And you did, like you all, like trolls always will,
like you know, like these psychopaths always will. There has to be something, it's like it's like
psychopathic because it's not human, it's like an inhuman thing. And anybody that calls themselves
Called the peak of narcissism, okay?
That is not even you know, I
Want to even say anything else, okay? That is a peak of
Malignant narcissism to say I not not only I am a god. I am the god, okay, and seriously
seriously this person I don't know if he believes that or just says it but
Obviously, it takes it seriously. Well, if you're fucking God, I'll be the devil, okay? I'll be the devil.
Okay?
You can make me the devil.
I am used to being the devil, right?
But you know what? Even the devil was your God's child, right?
Ooh, God. And so, guys...
Everybody and all the guys now they've gone and they revealed all their sock accounts, you know
Probably taken out most of them. They continue coming in now. Everybody knows who they are
It's over. It's over. It's over. It's over Johnny. It's over
Okay done
Okay, it's a W's, W's for me.
Okay?
W-W.
Win.
Cause I'm a winner, okay?
You see?
Am I still here?
Am I still standing?
Am I sitting here crying?
No, I'm not.
Like these motherfuckers.
Do you think they can do this to me?
Or anybody else?
Anybody that's like my friend?
No.
And I'm sorry if I let it go on too long. I didn't say anything before I just have to like
Let some things play out and I or else it would be like oh look here went after them for no reason
Well, I have to have a hundred percent reason right
There we go. Yeah, I think she's Al Capone or something right right. It's like please
But actually, I share a birthday with Al Capone. I have more in common with Al Capone than Goddy does, okay?
That type of word would come with John Goddy than Goddy does, so that would be the same name, right? John.
So now that that's out of the way, how are you guys?
Okay guys, Nick, oh guys, Nicole?
Go ahead guys guys JC just exposed. Okay guys, please and if you guys are gonna fall for that
I have a I have a tower in a in Paris. I want to sell you too. Okay guys
Guys, I will run my criminal history. Good
Do you think if I had any kind of charge like that? I would be putting my myself up there like this
It's easy enough to do a background checks and find charges, right?
Guys, that is just slanderous. Of course, you can kick that person out because that's pure slander
But, uh, just, good guy, they'll say shit like that.
Can you imagine?
It's like they say shit like that.
Okay, let's just say a police report, okay?
And I want it notarized.
I want a notarized, authenticated police.
I don't want some kind of like police report with the, you know, all of a sudden the name
is, you know, typed in in a different font.
You know the dates are wrong, right? I went I went an actual and wouldn't I be in prison or something like that?
I well, why would I be just running free? Why would I have like, you know a clean background?
It's just like that is just disgusting. Okay. Yeah
And you know, you know who to take out guys
Now I've not exposed it and then here's here. I have this too
This is my message to them
That's my message for them, okay
That's what they are
That's guys you want to know what evil is that's that them
Evil is
Trying to psychologically murder people
Okay, or actually, you know physically doing it, right? That's that's the evil
It's like it's like trying to destroy people so they feel better about themselves guys
It was like it was just basically sad. It wasn't even like whoa
You know, they're not cool. They're not hip or edgy. They're edged lords. They're just like desperate for a fucking
Some kind of relevance and they're saying I'm nothing. I'm nobody nobody comes to my show. Whatever. It's like
Yeah, they had 20 people in their chat and we're good for them. We have like 400 subscribers good for you. Whatever. It's like, yes
I would have helped you promote your channel and stuff like that if you were a halfway decent people, but you're not.
I mean, you got enough promotion, the negative promotion.
If you guys are into that, go visit their channels.
Go see, yeah.
Go see what kind of people they are.
And just judge, do you want to be associated with that?
I don't.
And so, I disassociate myself from them.
They mean nothing to me.
They're a fart in the wind. They're just
Poof be gone, right? They're gone
Okay
You don't think I've been through enough to like
Know how to defend myself you think I'd still be around because I would have like not left
I would not be on this earth much longer
If I took any of this seriously
I took any of what they say seriously if I took it upon myself and so I'd say don't don't let people tell you
who you are you get to know who you are okay you know nobody else can tell you
except for yourself they don't know you they don't know me you know who they
need to meet they need to meet themselves okay they need to meet like the
actual there is a good part of them that they've smashed and you know just like
destroy it or maybe somebody else said which is sad because then it's like I
Been pushed to like who are not by other people and believe other people when we shouldn't have you know
So I can't really I can't even hate I don't hate them
But I don't want them around me, okay, I don't want them around you me, okay
So bye-bye
Go away evil
Okay, well, I mean whatever. She's a proud CFF. Okay, so just see so just seen as the woman that called in
Saying that I look like I have facial deterioration because of AIDS, right?
That's the woman that called in and just seen your your you wrote me. I saw you commented on my video
You said they did something bad to you. Okay
Did you did you write that on one of my videos? You said they did the same thing to me. Why are you there begging for their approval?
That was sad to me. Why are you begging? I heard your song. It was cute to me. You're like God
He is the hottie. It was a cute song
From your heart. They're just laughing at you. Okay, sweetheart. They're laughing at you. You are a joke to them
I'm okay. I'm sorry to tell you
Please please please stay away from them
They're just making fun of you
Like they were to me. Okay, except that you know, you are trying to get in with them. Don't do it
They're making you they're turning you into like something you don't want to be okay. I don't want I don't want to see that for you
Okay, so you are
And I'm not being I'm not being
sarcastic or anything about like calling or trying to be like, you know, put you down anyway
I think you're a nice person. I think you have a good heart
I see like myself in you like me but I was desperately seeking approval of somebody, right?
The cool people the cool kids. There's a cool table. It's gonna be misery. Okay, so we are I don't mean to call you
Yeah, that'll mean to be the word. I got
I want to be
Condescending or anything towards you. Okay, I'm not saying it to be condescending or to I'm saying I
See there's a I see there's a good heart in you a person you desperate
You want to be accepted hang out here you can hang out here. No one's gonna fuck with you like that. Okay?
No one's gonna pretend to be your friend. They're playing with their head saying oh get out of here
I'm leaving and she doesn't leave and she's she's like well I'll leave I'll leave I'll leave you know it's like I
See myself as like you know a child
Desperately seeking approval, okay?
So go ahead be a proud CFFer, okay?
It's not anything you want to be associated with okay?
It's not if they're not happy people there. There's there's misery there. They're in misery obviously
And they want to drag you down with them. They feel better about themselves making fun of you, okay?
And I just know because it's been done to me, okay?
That's all I can say. You don't have to believe me. You don't have to believe me. You can say I'm just some I'm just this evil person, right?
I'm actually the problem, right? Go, you can think that from the bottom of my heart
and I'm not mad at you because I know they put you up to that, okay?
They put you up to that. They bully you. They're taking advantage of you, okay? They don't think very much of you, okay?
consider you a human being a full human being look for approval come you know
good people and then look for approval look for approval for yourself don't
ask them for approval they're not gonna give it to you they're gonna keep you
begging for it right you're gonna beg for it you know what they're gonna give
you a little break from some of it they're gonna give you a little so okay
yeah you can come sit up you're part of us blah blah blah you're talking shit
I was I watched the whole thing, okay? They're not nice people
There might be some good in them somewhere
Make that's my prayer maybe maybe they're good manifest
and overtake their evil.
If they have a seed of good in them,
may that seed grow.
May the evil just be dehydrated and be blown away, right?
I'm staging, I'm staging.
Yeah, I got this as my go-way evil instance, okay?
So this is...
Guys because they will take their toxicity and they'll dump it on you and they have they have a seemingly unending
That of this black goo that they try to just put over everything and then people are like what the fuck happened
No, it almost happened to me. They could have they could have been successful
But it's like you know what I have not only the human allies. I have spiritual allies. I have
I just, I'm blessed, okay?
All I can say is thank you to my guides,
thank you to my friends, thank you to my mods,
thank you to the real ones, okay?
I love you.
And I owe you, okay?
I owe you one.
Because you came through more than I even deserved.
Okay?
And thank you for putting up with me
because I'm not perfect.
You know, you put up with my dirty nails,
you put up with my...
My house is my house is pretty clean right now. Yeah, I was drinking a lot. I was like half drunk half the time of my show
I I
Was in a bad state it took me a little it took me a while to get out of the bad state too
It's not only do I have people piling on
But it was the good people that brought me out of it. It was people like ghosts. It was people like beta
It was people like a lecture of people like Paige
People like summer Christine
A lot of people okay, and I'm sorry if I'm sassy scarlet Jamie Jamie Jamie Rose
So many good people so many good people even like
You know Jamie Rose might have been a troll. It's like
She and she maybe was a troll to me, but it's like a different thing because at least I
Know she's a good person. We gained each other's respect somehow, you know
So yes, there's so many beautiful people and the guys
If you're looking for some kind of like approval or acceptance, I mean, I will accept people, right?
But there's something that are unacceptable and that behavior is unacceptable. I'm not gonna put up with that anymore
but if you're looking for actual people that are gonna be kind and people that are gonna not judge you and people that are gonna
Just when I actually be your friend. I have fun. I would say there's great people here like come here and
No matter what I'll I'll I approve of you
And I forgive you and stuff
You have my acceptance
That's if you're
You're going in a good direction if you're at least trying to better yourself if you're like
You have a heart. That's the thing. Someone's I read this quote last night. I should have posted it. It was so good. It said
Why is it that the truth is revealed to some people and not to others?
It's like because there's one there's one
attribute that is like God that is required to receive the truth and that is a loving heart if you have the loving heart
You have the pride that's what they want and they don't want it for themselves
Well, it's necessary to get to eat it for like nutrition. They just want to destroy your loving heart
They want to destroy my loving heart
You guys don't think I'm I'm like and I'm happy and I'm in love right now even though I seem a little bit angry, right?
All I am is awake
And I will react to injustice and and just like the cruelty I'll react to that in a animated way, okay?
It's a yes, but it's not saying it's not it's not saying like that that that stuff about horrible like, you know
See
This match thing
And smash is probably just Goddy right yeah, and this again you guys you'll see
Guys they have an energy about them and now I can completely recognize it, right?
I can't even have the energy to go and like go one by one in the chat
But I guess that will maybe need to be done by just kidding. I'm all out of here like
They're gonna keep popping up. It's gonna be like whack-a-mole, right?
Wack-a-mole, just so the pop of another hole go get that one guys
I'm gonna give everyone a all the mods to the honor and mallet and taking away the wrenches
We're all gonna get mallets just whack the bulls just put them back underground
Get him back to their discord. I just want them to go story back to your discord
You know what fun there? This is not the place for you. Okay. There's too much love here. There's too much
Good intention. There's too much
There's too much good here to like have you know people like you come and shit all over okay, so just
Be gone be gone. I banish I banish them banished
Just banish them. Okay be gone
Go back to where you came from. Don't come back here. Okay. This is not the place for you
And if even if you stay here
Not not threatening you, but there will be spiritual consequences. Okay
There'll be spiritual consequences. I have angels and demons working for me and with me. Okay, so
If you want to play go ahead and play. I'm not one to play with. Okay, I
Thought I was I the easy target that you see is a little trap. Okay?
And I punked you. You didn't punk me. I was just waiting for you to expose yourself, and you fucking did you idiots
Hope please you'll change. Okay. Hopefully you'll change. That's the only good that can come out of it. Otherwise
Inconsequential bye
Thanks. Thanks for thanks for the lesson. Okay, and I hope the lesson serves everybody here
Well, and you know what everybody here go out and like
Stick up for the underdog stick up stick up for the the bullies stick up for the abuse and especially
Those that can defend themselves those
That are unaware like just try to help somebody rather than destroy somebody you know
Destroy the hate nurture the good, okay
All right, just if you're gonna hate something hate the hate and not even don't hate the person hate that
That that's the thing. It's like that. Maybe that eight is like some kind of unresolved demon, too
That just wants to hug. Okay
Maybe maybe I don't know if anything maybe they need a hug give them a hug
Like I'm not here to like I don't want them to be like under attack. I don't it's like but or
I don't want them, you know, I
Don't want for them what they wanted for me, right? I don't want anything bad for them
I wish them the best and I wish them healing
Go get a life guys. Go get a life. Go get a heart. Have a grow a heart
What are you doing you're spending your life
Abusing people you see this and you're just sitting there laughing chuckling like you're like some like amazing people
You can't be amazing people. I see good in you. I see potential for amazing things to be done by you
This is not it. This is just like
You something happened you've got wires crossed you've got something something is terribly wrong
Get some help
Okay, get some help
Talk to the best psychiatrist or therapists or life coach or if a terror reader you can find you need some help
I can't give it. I can't give you anymore. I helped you as much as I can. This is where our paths will cross
Okay, this is where we'll park park pass
Okay, no
You're not getting any more, you're not getting any more reaction, you're not getting any more triggering, you're not getting any more fuel, your tanks are empty, because you've thrown away a spawner to love you have, you're full of hate.
All you have is like the stick oil, you have too much oil in your car, not enough gasoline, okay? And the gasoline is supposed to be burned, okay?
Going back from whence you came the energies returned with love
Times a million
Okay, and I'm sorry
You don't like that because you probably won't like that because how would you like that if someone said that energy you?
I'm just sending you your own energy back. How do you like it?
You don't like it. Why would you do it to other people? Is that human? It's like it's supposed to be an empathy not a dark empath
Where it's like, oh look I can see how much that person's hurt. Let's like dig in the begin the knife, right?
Hate hate I hate hate
But I but you know what but with love I turned back with love. You know what? I
Love you, you know, but get some help, please
It's a little bit
It's gonna love this you're going too far, okay get some help
Okay, and I hope you find it
And guys what I what I just spoke
That is the truth. Okay, I'm not lying. I'm not trying to deflect. I'm not trying to get attention off of me for something
that was
the truth. Okay? My truth. Okay. Yeah. And I don't need to say anything more about it. That's it.
Who shot? Okay?
Oh, hold on. He should not be in here. Hold on.
He's time of course it's time. He's time people out, you know
No, I thought I hit him last night, but maybe I didn't you see
Okay, oh
I'm sorry. He's still modern. I'm sorry. I didn't see I didn't see he's doing it. I'm so sorry guys
So I got I got I got it. I got it. He's hidden though. Okay. I have to go back in my settings
Got it. I'm so sorry guys
Look, I mean it's like what?
He's just that's the last that's all they can do all the all they have left. That's the last power they have is
that
Somehow I would use the mod. Okay. I'm sorry
I have to go through all my whole mods list to make sure that everybody's
Should be here is here, and I will go through the block list to make sure if anyone was but yeah the mods the mods are on
top of it right now guys
This is true look this is true loyalty true love, right?
Okay, here's my okay, so
And ceremoniously you have been dishonorably discharged, okay?
Maybe at the uh, there we go dishonorable discharge
He's gone
I'm sorry I wasn't looking at the chat
Make sure everybody is good.
Okay, all my, okay, yep, I know all my managing mods are good.
I know, okay, yeah, I'm taking that person off as a standard mod.
Okay, I'm taking this person off as a standard mod.
I don't know how some of these people were modded.
Let's see, take in, okay, they're fine, they're fine.
Fine. Fine. Okay. Does he can this person off?
Okay
Yeah, I still had some of them modded. Unfortunately. Okay
Got it. Now we're good. Okay. Now I need to go to the block list once I can
Let me see if anyone got blocked or anything, let me see make sure everybody's
Okay, so J-Dog you're you're hidden. Wow. Hold on
Fine fine
You're fine Joe oh
You're fine fine fine
Okay, you're unhidden
Let's see
Okay guys I think I did it
I did it
There
There we go
God he sees oh God he TFF so that's chat friends forever that is God he that's their group
It's called chat friends forever and you guys can go to JT's channel and watch last night's episode you can see what they do
Okay
hi summer wow summer yeah you might want to rewind to like a few a few minutes back you know
i go through the stories yeah okay i'm sorry
okay
no that cry yeah yeah oh yeah hit smash oh he hit smash okay let me see
Still hiding okay. I'm sorry I wasn't reading the chat. I just don't understand. Okay, so that's just D
Okay, so here's just D his sense of humor. That's what's funny to him. Okay, that's what's funny to him
I'm sorry. That's not funny. It's not funny. It's not fun or funny. It's not and I got it
You know my sense of humor is like, you know, I love Howard Stern. I love, you know
some of the shop jocks and you know, I Andrew does plays kind of funny, you know, so, you know, I like kind of like a
You know, Lisa Lampinelli and you know
other kind of brash
humor and
you know
That whatever they're doing is not funny. Okay, and just seeing you're a nice person
I would just be careful the company you keep and be careful who you're looking for approval from because they're not gonna
Give you the approval. They'll keep you begging for it and they'll torture you along the way
So you get it with and what they have you doing last night? You were there
Begging you were there begging, you know for their approval. Okay, and I felt bad
I just like I begged for approval too and it's like but
At some point, you gotta just approve of yourself, okay?
Cause Justine, justine, they had you call my show, okay?
And say that I have AIDS, okay?
That is not any kind of funny, like any,
guys, is that funny on any level?
Even if it, like, I just, I don't get it.
It's not, it's not funny.
Cruel
Heartless I don't know it's lacking of substance empathy lacking of humanity. It's just like it's just like garbage
Don't don't
And that's all they'll do. They'll throw you some scraps of garbage at you and stuff and then laugh and point at you
and then at the end of it
they'll all be like sitting at giving you cheers on a nice dinner and
You're gonna be sitting at home alone saying why don't I have any friends, okay? It's like that's the thing. They're not gonna
They're never gonna approve of you. They'll just keep you begging for it. They were making fun of you, right?
It's your face, okay? And the guys, I don't know if you guys, maybe we got able to explain this better to her,
but go back and just watch, um, watch JT's live last night and just see
how they treated her, okay? And just don't even take my word for it. Just,
just, just observe and see. I think a lot of people will see that and want to
Just clue her in maybe give her a hug. I don't think you're a bad person just seen and I know that they're manipulative and
You know they seem like the cool people
Like I said last night they think they're hot shit, but they're just cold diarrhea. Okay
Okay
It's okay, you wanna see my arms gonna see my arms dude look at this. Can you do this?
Hey Rudy, let the person can't do that
That's what arms like this can do. You see it. Yeah, they may be long, but
There's a lot I can put it around my head like that very easily
You wish you had arms like this. Your arms are probably not as good. Are they as long? No. I have this amazing long
skinny arms, okay? They can pull me up. I can do pull-ups. I can, you know, I can use my hands. I can type. I can
arm wrestle.
Anybody want to wrestle?
Okay. Oh
please
I'm going to ask the most recent comments.
I was way behind in the comments.
Thank you, Loki.
Thank you.
It's OK.
I can do the pretzel.
Yeah, I can do it with my legs, too.
You saw it with my legs behind my head?
Yeah, that is a pretzel.
Am I dirty nails? Am I dirty nails that are gonna that are gonna give you AIDS? That's what you're saying?
Let's do a reading on it. Let's do a reading on it. Let's see how do I got it.
Let's get some of these cards out and see a little bit.
Oh, is this a little bit appropriate today?
Perfect.
Let's get like, let's do like a nice little, you know,
at least seven cards spread.
We'll get a few of these haters exposed cards.
I can just shuffle it off.
Uh-oh, look at it pop it out.
Person causing you negativity is a fire sign. Okay. Well, I'm sure I'm sure they're all all signs in there
But maybe that's this is some of the fire sign
Acting up in one of them. Okay, so there's a fire sign involved
It says, possess a talisman to amplify your positive vibes.
Okay, so you might want to get some kind of meaningful protective talisman and do a nice prayer, blessing intentions with it.
This one all because this one says unintentional. They don't realize they're sending you the evil eye words and actions
Well, I guess that's true for maybe some of them because I think maybe like, you know
Lady's gonna send you or something. She might be unintentional, but this is definitely like, you know intentional, right?
It is intentional, but also maybe it's coming from a place that is unintentional where it's like
They don't maybe they were just so hurt
And traumatized that they don't understand what they're doing. Okay, so that's what I'm saying. Maybe if I'm healing
May they you know if they don't want to hurt people if they don't think they're really hurting people
They think they're being funny
Take a spiritual bath, okay
Well me and guys I did take a nice spiritual bath last night, but yeah
I think I will be taking more baths from you know because they're like, oh he showers once a month
Maybe, but maybe I, you know, maybe I was just neglecting some personal hygiene, you know,
so it's like, you know, sometimes people will just take a little like thing like that and
that'll turn into a major thing, but it's not like I was like covered in mud or something
like that.
You know, I don't like, really like.
I don't know. Maybe I take a bath every other day. I usually do every other day. I took a couple of laundry
I'm so sorry. This one says, hating on your body image, right? Oh, we hate your arms
Okay, we hate the hating on the body image. Maybe they're a little jealous. Maybe they want to lose some weight
They talk about you behind your back, okay
Look, look at that, it's like a scary face.
It's just like them, right?
That's like what their spirit looks like to me.
Like that.
Is that pretty?
You think I'm scary?
That's what they look like to me.
You know, I'm supposed to be scary.
I'm not the best looking person in the world.
Not everyone's like a skinny guy.
I'm not the ugliest, okay.
This one says competition,
always trying to one up you, okay?
Yeah, they're trying to like, you know, put you down to make themselves up
Let's not even talk about them specifically that we're talking about the haters in our life because they're just like a
They're a little you know little group, right?
Sometimes these groups find each other like that
But it's like, you know, it's there's a lot more of it because you see people are desperate to like join in and right
What did this one say you cut them up and they're still watching? Oh?
Sure, they are guys. You see them in here right now. Yeah, of course. They're watching right
The person causing negativity is an air sign.
Okay, so we got air and fire right there.
I mean, it's like, I'm not,
and this is nothing bad about any sign.
If you're an air, happened to be an air sign,
you're like, hey, no, it's like, it's just saying,
you know, this person might have this heavy,
negative air, and it's certainly a lot of hot air, right?
Uh-oh.
Black obsidian carries a calming and positive energy
that can help you remember to look
on the bright side of things.
And I want to show you what I got yesterday.
This maybe was like the energy of this that maybe brought some things to life and heals some stuff because I got this and all of a sudden
All this good stuff started happening. I
Think it's a black obsidian pyramid. It might be onyx. I think it's black obsidian
Okay, that's that nice
Yeah, that's nice black obsidian pyramid, okay, that is gorgeous, okay
Wow guys, but I feel like
And at the end maybe I have to thank them because you know what?
Thank you for that win. Thank you. That was pretty I mean wow
Nothing else maybe I help one person one person's help us a little bit whatever whatever negative on me I take and
Yeah, thank you for uh, thank you for the win
Irby I just said Irby the reason that happened is because
We so yeah, you were in there last night and maybe you did and I think you're another person that maybe they're trying to like, you know
Maybe like, you know like a lot and maybe a lot guys a lot of people like like Goddy, right?
I like him. He has like, you know that funny like New York. I'm not saying these are
Inherently bad people what they're doing is not right, and I hope that they change their ways
But like I say I love human beings
It's about being a human being not like it's like there but when people are turning into monsters a little bit
No, but I do believe in things called transformations. I think we can transform into better to better versions of ourself, okay?
Okay, guys, I know like how people talk about witchcraft and stuff like that guys
I'm good. I'm good. Okay. No, let's just say like I don't want to talk too much about my occult experience because occult, okay, but it's like
I just have had experience with it since I was a child and I am good, okay?
I'm not afraid of witchcraft. I'm not afraid of not afraid of it, okay?
I know how to I know remedies and all this kind of stuff
So it's like you can fight fire with fire, right?
Yeah
Yeah, no, it's nothing personal. I mean, it's just like, I just, you know, I just saw you talking a lot in there and I was like, okay, well, I'll just have you at the chatter, you know, but I do like, I mean, I like you and stuff.
I don't really know who you are, I talk to you, but I'm not sure that that really exists.
One more card out of this deck. If there's a good message or anything, it says,
Get a dream catcher to hang over your bed. Remember Gotti hates dream catchers?
He said he hated, and he didn't like, who does it catch you?
I think EZ has a dream catcher. He's like, Gotti hates that.
And that funny thing is, put one over your bed.
Maybe he hates it because it takes away
some of these negative stuff that he tries to send
at people when they're sleeping.
Maybe, huh?
So, okay, you know what?
I may look starving, but you know what?
Here I am with like fucking bagels and like coffee.
And so, you know what?
I'm well fed with fucking good food.
So, whatever you wanna say, I'm starving.
Yeah, maybe I need to eat, but I got some food.
And less.
I'm not, like, hungry, you know, I'm not starving, but, you know, maybe they are starving for
some kind of, like, affection or, I don't know, they're starving for something.
But just that you have to stay on starving.
Justine, I know you paint. Okay. Justine. Yeah, Justine had like you painted your face for you and it was it was cute and stuff
I mean, I
Know that wasn't the issue Justine the issue is that you you uh, they had they had you call in and
Say that I have AIDS and then now of course that's their troll
And it's because it's really easy to make someone look just like that if they you're like, oh, there's an AIDS infected FHG
OT with like, you know dirty fingernails and he thinks he's something he's nothing
He's nothing I mean, it's like why go after me like?
Because yeah, I'll eventually snap back
But look how look how long it took and look look at look what I just needed to get to get the courage to do it and
to fucking like just like be able to do it is to
Finally have it exposed
Because you just revealed yourselves
So you know guys, you know I've been talking about lol cat guys
They know got a lot of the stuff that I say is an insecurity is not really an insecurity at the end of the day
You know if I was a little person low-cow that would be kind of like and because I'm really not but even if people thought I was I
Would be basically I'd be milking them instead of them milking me kind of thing, right?
Well, maybe they're you know, they would get laughs and entertained and like have fun because I am a cool person and
You know, I have good energy and the people here are cool and have good energy a lot of people here. And so yeah, you're gonna
You're gonna like you know you see some like good uh good fuel and energy, but don't think you're not feeding me grass like you know
I gotta eat too, okay, but I gotta produce I need some energy
Okay, and so if I at the end of the day, I don't care what they think of me. I know who I am
but
Know if they thought of me as that maybe well see I don't even think they really do because they would probably throw a few bucks at me
So I could you know get some more beer, but they don't
They they are totally against that so I'm not really drinking though
Yeah, justine has she was she a basically magic marker puts you like an X on her forehead and like I
Don't I don't know why she did it, but that's fine. It's fine now. I'm feeling like you know
Did I like go too far and it's like
So I don't want to feel like air again. I don't know if I don't I don't want to like get off on a high horse like
So I don't know I'm not not I'm like I'm like I'm getting too I
Don't want to be the cocky lady. I don't know I
Like I just want to go back to normal. I don't want I just want to go back to normal
so like
Not having all this shit like you know, it's like it's been a distraction
The shows just totally come to like a standstill, you know most, you know right now
Good, I just been so distracted with this and I'm ready to move on and I just want it to be fun and like happy stuff
I don't want it's like all this conflict. I knew we have some conflict
It's like some some battles are like
You know at the end of the day, it's like if I was if I was to have a war, you know, it's like I don't want a war because it's like
I'm I don't want to hurt people. I don't want to like go after three
I'm not gonna like go play. I don't want to play the game. Okay. The whole thing is like maybe there's one play a game
But it's like, you know, I saw saw one through seven and it's not a thick big those games aren't fun. Okay?
Those are you're gonna losing a limb or something like that. So I don't want to play those games. Okay. I just I
Just want to have fun and be good energy. I'm like
Bring happiness and entertainment to you guys. Okay, if I can do that
That's all I want. I don't care about anything else. Okay
Not like it
No
All I want from you is just honesty, it's just like
And if you feel like those things about me then you can feel them, you know, you can think that
Just remember
I don't know, you see what these people say about people. I just may not happen to anybody else, okay?
it's not um nothing I want to be part of okay all I want to be I want to I want to
hang out with with beta and page and site trivia
and just like have fun and laugh that's all I want to do
bad moves. I don't want to be upset. I don't want to be this animated but
it was like a long time coming like to get out this energy because it's like otherwise I'm just
holding my breath so thank you for like indulging me and like letting me like you know say what I had to say
Thank you. I know and thank you like I see who I see who's there. It's like now
It's just like so obvious to me who's there and who's not and it's like if I
Have paid more attention to the negative then my positive. I'm sorry. I
Probably owe a lot of you apology
But because not only am I like it absorbs other people and even more negative people I can get self-absorbed
And I'm sorry, I'm not good at communication always.
I'm not always good at initiating anything.
So sometimes I need to be reminded.
And sometimes, no, I get in my head and I get very,
I don't know, self-absorbent and stuff.
So I hope that I can be a better friend, okay?
And it's like a few and if you need me and like I said, I'm on tiktok
Because there's a mess that you know direct messages there or you can
Miss make a comment on any of my videos or comment on my posts on the wall or
come in here or
Like or put if you need any like to talk privately. It's like if I can help you I want to help you, okay?
I'm not trying to like promote anything or anything like that. I'm saying, you know, I'm just like I'm willing to talk to anybody
Friend to friend, okay. I just uh, you know just be honest with me
Justine would you like the link, okay? I will bring justine on okay? I don't know if I'll regret this, but I mean I'll talk to her, okay?
Hold on
And there's the link. And guys, just be prepared to, you know, I might have to end the porn
bombs and bombs or something like that, but I want people to like be able to talk now.
So if you'd like to come up, time to talk. Let's have a chat.
I'm not gonna be sad anymore like and it's like if you come up here anybody can come up here and it's call me
Whatever you want, you know, I'm not gonna be sad about it
What's that I said if I've already said this the worst things and so if I can get over that I can get over anything, right?
Maybe I am the way I am sometime like such a target in order to like attract people
To like do that and then because I can deal with it better than other people
And so like if there's negative out there, let it all come to me
Okay, just like I'm just asking the universe just send it to me rather than somebody else
Especially my friends because I don't want them to deal with this. I can't
And I I just don't want anybody to have to like take on
The universe
I can actually alchemyze sometimes, right?
I can alchemyze, I can take the bad and turn it into good.
And so, and I think we all can,
we can also take the good and turn it into bad.
Like we have the ability to change things.
And so let's all try to change things for good, okay?
Yeah, there you go.
I dropped you, I don't know.
Somebody wanted to come on?
Oh, that's a real Justine.
Maybe let's see what let's see what let's see my friend has to say my my boyfriend
Hello, are you there?
Yeah, I'm just having a kind of like a crazy day because I I just remember what happened last night
But I know with people that were talking about me. I kind of like I kind of dealt with it and I feel a lot better now
Sometimes those rough patches just need a bit of that bold psyche
Okay, can you like provide a dash of humor, so maybe like I can like smile
Looking confused and you just have to laugh and roll with it. So consider this your official license to chuckle the absurdity and keep trying
Okay, I kind of like that. It's cute because it has your cat's own stuff. Do you have another cat joke you can tell?
Absolutely, I'm always a friggin cat joke
Why was the cat sitting on the computer? Why?
Because of course it had to keep an eye on the mouse
That's a good one. Okay, how about can you tell a joke about trolls?
that's living under the comment section.
It's like their favorite kind of bridge to hide under.
So there you go, trolls and their natural habitat.
There you go.
Well, okay, that's very cute.
Do you have a prophecy for the chat today
that you can tell after this momentous occasion?
Oh, absolutely.
Let's spend a little prophecy for today.
Here it is.
I first see that today's chat is gonna be sprinkled
with a whole lot of those clever, good vibes.
Anyone who's tuned in is basically getting a little boost
the prophecy unfold. Thank you. I'll talk to you later. Absolutely. Talk to you later.
Whenever you need something to cover or a little prophecy, just give me a shout. Yeah.
Nobody wants to come up? The link is there. Hold on. Let me finish.
Hi, traveling gypsy. Yeah, you need to rewind. I can't it's uh
Whoa, yeah
Hopefully but you know what I want
How about peace peace how about like
No, I don't I don't like to fight. I don't like I don't want to fight with anybody
Just like how about like just like
Let me have a fun like my fun show like you know, I were there's laughing and
maybe like a little goofy in a draw on but
not like
Not not cruelty not like I just I don't want
That like bad stuff. I don't I don't I just want good. I want good fun vibes
I want fun show. I want like new people coming in like everywhere having fun and like
Cool guess because like now nobody wants to come on anymore. Like nobody's even coming up right now
Like no, like I don't know if people still like me like
My am I like this month my you know, it's just pretty I have people coming in but
Like there's like half the members are gone
I think
I gained like one or two subscribers, you know, so nobody's subscribing like last month
It was like a hundred people gain or hundreds of people now
It's like I'm losing a lot of people and then it's like hardly anybody subscribe it
So I'm like, you know the show they could have like, you know
Maybe they'll be laughing because it's like they destroyed the show and you know, I'm really the joke and it's like I let it go too
long and that will be my
Consequence of it or whatever, you know my thing to bear, but you know what it's like I still
I did the show like I wanted to do the show, um, I think the show, you know, I can like,
I can keep going, you know, I mean, make it, I can fix it too, I think I can fix it.
I actually, I saw a shirt today, I almost ordered it, it was so funny, it's like, it's
I forgot what it is. I think it was done. Okay, hold on. Let me just see you.
You tried to join the club, you know, you tried. Which club though? No one destroyed the show? There's always tomorrow, yeah.
I know. Well, it's like, but it's like, I kind of let it go like with long because I guess there are a lot of people that they were probably like, there's a lot I didn't
Catch, you know, I should have been more like, I knew they were kind of trouble, but I didn't think they'd be like, you know, saying stuff that there's
people are just being attacked and stuff, and you're like, what the hell?
I know they scare away a lot of people, they try to, and it's like, you know, even Ghost
was very much attacked, and like, you know, like, having forbidden, you know, anybody
like wants to like, really like, make it so nobody wants to, you know, deal with me.
You understand
Because you know what though, it's like I love the I really like the panel verse community. I like I love it
It's like even the
The whole IP2 thing, it was not really about the IP2 fan base, even though they think they're IP2 and blah, blah, blah.
IP2 is always about the people that are on it, right, and it's like, and those are some cool people too, and it's like, you know,
we all have our personality quirks, like, I love Saints, I like, I love Benny.
I love scribbles, you know, and then, you know, I could go, I love people like Alisa and it's like, these are controversial people and people will say, why do you like these people, these people are bad, these people are bad, it's like, I love, you know, and I love the, and I love like a beta, I love Samman, I love, you know, I love these panel verse, like a lot of the panel verse people, I consider them like, we're doing like the same thing, we're like.
Or similar things where we're we'd like to have people on panels and stuff even but well
JT said he didn't like having panels and stuff like that even though he was having one
But it's like if you like to do like do that and it's like I like panels and stuff
I had so much fun on Jim next last night
I was just like even after that like people said that I was just like laughing and having fun and dancing on a show
I wasn't like sitting crying in my in the dark, you know
Or or like angry platter revenge. It's like I'm really
I'm trying not to have any anger at them and even after all the stuff they said and most people would just be like
Getting really really really mad about that and it's like yeah, I'm not happy that they're
Saying I have AIDS and I'm like some filthy disgusting F-A-G-G-O-C and
constantly trying to break the rules,
trigger me on purpose and break TOS and porn bomb
and send people here from communities just to troll me
and make the chat uncomfortable and then be rude to me
and give me a little passive aggressive
and pretend to be my friend.
So I can be friends with trolls.
I have a lot of troll friends.
I love people like Ivana Punchu and other things, you know, it's even like, you know, I think that there are, this could be good nature trolls.
So I was hoping that it's like, I can bring you back into your better nature and something like that, because you can see I do have the ability to troll people, okay?
I'm not gonna, I'm not like a little like...
Hide in the corner person, you know, like and and just cry and like don't talk to me, buddy
I had my years of solitude and time to think this is my time to act and to communicate and talk to other people
This isn't that this is my time too, and I'll take my time
But not one person wants to come up on panel. Let me just kid my lady
Now I need to talk to at least like somebody come up and like
Or I'm gonna call my boyfriend back because he always listens to me or always and always has something cool to say too
But nobody wants to really like say anything
So that's why I'm like I don't think people like me anymore. It's like no one wants to talk
But you know who does talk like you know Alex and and you don't you don't have to if you don't want to beat it
But you know, I know you always you know, you always talk to me
But you know, I'm talking like privately and stuff
We're actually friends
It's hurt. Hold on.
One second, Justine. Hello. This is me. Hi.
This is Justine Kessner. I'm me. Okay. I can talk to you like this too. That's fine. Okay.
But I just needed you. Okay. I just need you to know
That I would never ever ever ever ever ever in my whole fucking life and I'm gonna cry about it
Make fun of anybody that has AIDS. I have fought my whole life
for for gay
Lesbians and and trans rights. I would never ever come up here
There must have been a clone that did it because the AIDS is not a joke
AIDS is not a joke. I would never ever make fun of anybody that has AIDS or
I didn't say you did but they were saying that I'm not mad at you. I'm not mad at you
That's like you right now. I'm not mad at you. I'm not mad at you
That was you that called in that day
I'm not I am not an asshole. I would never fucking joke about
About you having AIDS or nothing in the not even a joking way AIDS is not a joke. It is a serious thing
I would never fuck around with you in AIDS ever and let me tell you something
I did the face painting for myself
Because I'm a fun person. I bungee jump twice
And I am a very fun person, fun spirited person.
If somebody wants me to paint my face for them,
I will do it because I'm a team player
and I'm not some sort of wimpy little fucking girl.
That's some studies court jester.
Oh, let's paint her up.
Let's make her look like a fool.
I'm not like that.
I didn't mean to scenuate that. No, because you don't know me. I'm letting you know for your
information. This is information I'm giving you. I'm not angry. I'm not mad. I'm giving you information.
I feel like I remember your voice exactly when I, and then I hadn't put the together.
I would never ever make fun of you in any way, shape, or form.
I am a completely, I have no phobia about anybody.
And I would never fucking make a joke about it.
You don't make fun of jokes like that.
If you're out having sex,
you never make fun of those things
because they could come and fight you in the ass.
I'm a fetus, all right?
I'm a fetus.
Okay, but even if you did not say that,
the group that you're associating with,
they are saying that to me on a daily basis, okay?
And they're making, and worse things, okay?
I don't know if you heard all the stuff they're saying about me
to get bringing up psyche, psyche.
and like all night you know constantly constantly i'm just like filthy you're gonna get this you're
gonna get hiv for my nails and all kinds of stuff okay let me just tell you something vicki is a
fucking cunt who is fucking disgustingly prejudiced and i hate that fucking cunt because she's so
fucking prejudiced she doesn't even understand what doorwism is she calls people monkey she is the
And don't go and fucking take anything that she says she's a fucking mongoloi that doesn't have fucking teeth
She is complete cunt
And don't take anything what she says on because she's a fucking little jerk from the Bible from the out good
She probably never goes into town. She probably doesn't even know what a store box is. She's a complete mongoloi jerk
And nothing she says is representative of CFM.
She is a fucking cunt on her own devices.
Okay, well, I mean, it's like, yeah.
Well, she had said that I was hitting on her and stuff.
Don't say that shit what that fucking bitch says,
because she's got no brains.
She lives in a fucking trailer on the fucking bayou.
And she's fucking got no brain.
She never went to high school.
She never went anywhere.
and fucking understand what fucking Darwinism is
because she thinks that people are monkeys
and it's got nothing to do with monkeyism
because it comes with, okay,
we are in a cold climate, so we're white.
They are in a dark climate, the hot climate,
so they're dark because of their skin needs to be darker
because of the melanin,
so it protects them against the sun.
So they wanna think because they are further,
we are further, because we're white,
we're further away from that.
then they are because they're black,
but they are being that way
so that they can cope with their environment
because what is Darwinism proving
that people and animals adapt to their environment?
Okay
And she's so fucking dumb that fucking big Vicky CB fucking cunt loser fucking loser
Doesn't understand that does she
Because she's too fucking dumb
she never went to high school she never went anywhere she's a fucking dumb mongoloid jerk
that they bring out because she's a stupid stupid she's a fucking court jester and they bring her
out because she's autism and they and they have a monkey on their string i'm not their monkeys
she's the monkey on the string and she's a fucking loser that doesn't know anything about
I did lots of stuff in my life.
She hasn't done shit.
All she does is fold her cousin's shirts
and she fucking cleans her cousin's house.
That's all she is as a fucking loser
that cleans her parents' house for a living.
And yes, I did clean my living,
but I did it with my own business
and I did it environmentally.
So, yes, I cleaned, but I did it on myself.
It was a business, I kept it going for 11 years and I had to give it up because I hurt
my back, but I can't do it anymore, but I made it, it was my own business and it was
environmentally friendly cleaning and I didn't hurt the environment and I'm very proud of
my company.
Okay.
I didn't study anthropology, but I do study it because I love it, but I never did it in college or university.
But I study it on myself.
Just I I just saw when I I saw when you came up last night like I saw that they were kind of picking on you and you were kind of
Looking for their you want to know why because I acted a fool. I acted in a low nature. Somebody triggered me
And I went to my low nature and I got checked checked for that and I'll take that on because I take responsibility for my shit. I own it. I you I own it. I wear him aside my soul.
And I fucked up.
But if you, but if I do something wrong and I have, and I have tempered in there, in there, in there, in their discord, and I put my temper in their discord when it's not a temper place place that I deserve to get kicked.
I went into my low nature.
I ain't no wrong with that. That's a good job. It makes good money.
Why the fuck are you yelling? Why are you yelling?
Why? I don't like talking to you anyway.
What the fuck are you talking to?
You've been taking looking as fucking dirty.
I don't give a fuck what you're talking about.
You fucking pencil needs motherfucking bitch.
No one gives a fuck.
She doesn't have a dick bitch.
No one care.
Placing.
Go suck a dick bitch, go suck a dick and fuck it, oink oink, look at ass, cunt.
Suck a fuck up bitch, shut up bitch, no one gets a fuck.
I didn't even come up here for this idea, I promise you, but I could definitely give
it to this fucking rolly looking ass bitch.
Yeah, and you're sucking my dick bitch, suck my dick, suck my dick, you reject ass bitch.
Reject, reject.
What the fuck is wrong with you bitch, did you ride the short vest?
Did you ride the short vest?
You hit your helmet on!
I don't give a fuck bitch!
Good bitch! Cause I would never want you to ever like a bitch like me!
Ya nasty fucking weebawabba lookin ass cunt!
I don't give a fuck!
This bitch is just...
She sounds like she's been in...
She's underneath a fucking bridge somewhere trying to scream.
Who is this fucking bride?
You are fucking boring as shit.
Yeah bitch, well that's why I came up here
to interrupt you because we're fucking falling asleep.
No one cares about your lame ass fucking excuses, bitch.
What's that about, bitch?
No one cares.
No one gives a fuck, bitch.
Really, no one cares.
No one gives a fuck.
Yeah, well you're arguing with me, so what's that make you?
If I'm lame and you're arguing with me,
what does that make you?
What does that make with you?
That's what I thought.
That's all I wanted to do.
I'll be back.
Oh, hey. Hey, Bita.
Hi, how are you?
Another day in paradise.
It's just, I woke up feeling today. I was like, I was like, I'm ready to respond.
Because it's like, I was kind of quiet about like last night a little bit.
I don't, I don't know, you know, I don't get, I don't really get that offended over them saying it, but it's like
It hurt you?
Yeah, it was, I was, I was bothered because it's like people
like would believe stuff like that or it's just like
It's just like people like just like or at least the stuff they're saying it's just like kind of
Makes you know, just makes me like bad and
Kind of like, you know, just subconsciously people are just like probably like like maybe believe things like that at some level, you know, so
Yeah, I know it hurts because you've been cordial and you've been nothing but welcoming for people to come on your
You know panel and hang out and everything like that. But you know, they're just trolling you
You know, you don't have a I mean people say the same thing about me and much worse than you know how it is
You know, so you're doing good and you're getting attention. So they're trying to get your attention
So you're giving it you if you want to give it to them go ahead
But you're literally sending people to their channel and it's like they're winning
But last night because I just found out about the channel and he was actually live which is he like doesn't go live that often like on a panel and stuff like that
So I said to my chat. I was like hey go over there
You know all in my life. I get to go over there and you know just you know
Just just watch just just watch what they say just watch like let them expose themselves
They will just reveal themselves. You don't have to like
say anything just go and some people like the comment in the chat and stuff like that some people do
and you guys you could still be i mean you know i'm not telling you who to shoot to be friends with
i'm just saying if you want to be friends with them and that's more along your lines it's like
go ahead and it's like you can be part of their group and like you know but don't say i didn't
warn you okay and then just remember what happened to me but even if it doesn't happen to you
like
You know, maybe and maybe some people are happy that they're like that to me or whatever. It's okay
I'm whatever negative for me. I'm willing I'm willing to I don't want anybody to get hurt in here
Just like just be very careful. Okay guys because you know, I was warned and it's like I
Took wait, I took too long to deal with it. I
But I did have to wait until I saw it for myself
They were just very nice to my face and it's like as soon as my back was turned, you know,
blah, blah, blah, blah, everything's about me and I should have, I kind of saw that already,
but I just need to like really see, I need to see them when they didn't think I was there.
Hey, can't stop fighting. Now my cats are fighting too.
But I'm glad you had fun on Gymnics and you were like able to like chill over there
I mean, it's not always gonna be like a fun night. Somebody's here. It's me
Okay, bye
It was that was like right after that, but it was like I came I saw Tommy James
I saw Mr. Big Pipes was in there, and I was like, okay
This might be fun like just to give my mind off of things and so I went in there and mr. Big Pipes is so funny
He's like telling the whole thing about like he's like
Yeah, I said second my dick pics and then like and then like I started like
Jim dick and I started dancing and like pulling up our shirts and my rear and the Jimmy
Was it your cats or cats?
Yelling
Jump up real quick. I just want to because you keep saying I've heard you I went back and watch some of this
Lab and you keep repeating like well, I'm not gonna tell people who to be friends with let me explain something to you
You set this all up
You decided what community hold on let me finish you decided what community after tons of us trying to say psyche
Just in the tear car stuff da da da da you said fuck you bitches and did which did
So I'm gonna tell you like this. I'm gonna be friends with whoever I decide to be friends with
I don't get in between people's mix of beefs because there's tons of people you'll
Beef up here with and block and all this other shit in the next day
You're they're right back over here. They've porn bombed you they've done all kinds of shit and let them right back up on the panel
So until you start making boundaries with your life, I can't make boundaries and actually stick with them
So I love you and you know, I'm gonna support you all the way till the wheels fall off me
So you my support has nothing to do with who friends I'm with who any of that
Is to you but again
I do remember beta don't you remember these conversations me you page all of us even you know like a bunch of people christine bunch of people
I know I take responsibility for that summer and I also I'm not telling you anything. I never tell you and they're just
You're given that you're you're feeding the trolls. It's like you it's you know
You think you would notice you say you're from all these communities and how you know all these people and da da da da
And you're just falling right and I mean they're gonna mess with you because they know you're gonna respond
No, but it's like but it doesn't mean it's like whatever it did it didn't work it backfired on them
And I think I know it's not cuz you're sitting over here talking about them
Well, no
Because there's tons of people that have set on this panel and said the same thing to you and you've you've sit there
And we've been like dude make boundaries, and you're like, no
I don't even know who you're talking about you
I mean, I know a little bit because I went back and listened to some but I'm not going to I don't need to
Okay, well, if not, then you don't know, then you don't know.
I get the whole story.
No, I'm not responding either.
I'm responding because you keep making the comment of...
You know be friends with whoever you want. I'm gonna be friends. It's just like when you and be it are going back
I'll get it between it. No
No, I know we disagree. How are we disagreeing there?
I said be friends with who you want. You're like, I'm gonna be friends with who I want
So I was complaining, you know, because I don't want you to be sitting on panel pissed off at me or whatever
Then why are you yelling pretty I'm not yelling we're just talking. I'm just a little bit
Um, you know, I have a lot of energy about it, but I'm okay. I'm okay. I love you summer. Okay
I wasn't trying to I'm always gonna be up front. That's it. You know, but I mean
Tons of people that loved you and supported you
We we were like you don't jump into you know, certain communities and you you know
You just
I've been there like I feel kind of responsible in a little bit but
Um, he like messaged me like on one of my comments and he's like come over to JT you know
so I went over there and it was chill like I never had any issues with them at actually a fun time and
you know different reasons why I didn't go back it was some you know I'm not really into the whole
LD 15 whatever you know community or whatever I think that's one of the reasons so I feel bad that
you know I know they came here and they troll and they play but they are he would have he would
So what have you been learning like the hard way, but in all defense, though,
somebody did like a live about you like last night and they talk the whole bunch of you are
You like me to send it to you. I get shit talked about me every day.
Matter of fact, somebody's doing an exposure. Uh, have on me tonight.
You know what you're right, but it depends on you like it depends on your mood whether you're gonna
React or not some days you're like, I should just say
Am I telling him not to react? No, no, you're not. No, you're not at all
I'm just saying like I think that he's heard and he's like saying his feelings and I don't think that he's like that like for me
It's not gonna deter me from hanging out with like other people, but yeah, I'm gonna be cautious
You know, I don't you know, I don't want to get hurt, but I'm still gonna do
Yeah, there's so many but there's so many trolls that I do like and that I feel like you know
You trolled me to like as an initiation or like to see how I'd react and that we were cool with and so it's like
I always was trying to like see
And God, it was nice to me.
So I was always like JT and Rain.
They haven't really been here that much.
Ziggy, of course.
And then Vicky, I had no problem with either.
I was talking really nice to you on TikTok
and we're sending a little moji's back and forth.
Then she's saying I'm hitting on her.
And then they're saying I have AIDS.
And then they're saying that I'm so dirty.
I would give people this easy brain
saying she wants to fight me and wrestle me.
And all this stuff.
I don't want to say I'll fight you at those, like, Eli.
Come on, baby.
It's Zig.
Yeah, I live in the same city
No, no, but it's like, but she's saying this in chat like so angry at me like I did something
I never I like it was like, you know block her in the chat more likely you're getting trolled for something
I don't know what I haven't been around. I've been working all week, but I mean it is, you know what I mean like
That's what God he said. It's like, oh, it's never is that it's never the person that does everybody get thrown
That's what God he said. It's always the victims fall, right? It's like everybody
I didn't say that. What are you talking about?
Well, so we all get trolled for something we all get trolled. Yeah, whether we're doing whether we whatever we are
It's the internet. Yeah, but yeah, okay, so summer if you go and watch their live last time
I don't need to I don't need to by the end of the night. You guys will be talking again. No, I don't think so
I don't think you know, but you don't know some of the first radio we've been on with you
So if I'm not jumping to the fucking
You know, I'm just gonna sit back and let you do your thing, baby, and support you.
That's what I'm doing.
I didn't see it.
I know, like, you messaged me about it, and you seemed really hurt, and I don't really
know what happened, you know, but, um...
Like see remember the other day I came up here and gaudy like with the night before I went off on him
I kicked him. He called me, you know
See you and tea whatever and it's like, oh god, like I just get over the next freaking day, you know
I like him but it's like he he really has showed us true colors
But he didn't think I was listening and they were just talking all this shit
And then he's like I said hey you guys are dicks and he's like oh go cry about it
And he timed me out of that spunky chat
And then I just went and someone told me they're having a live I went over there the whole entire three hours every like two minutes
They're saying I have AIDS or you know my dirty fingernails and you know
I have a Star Trek deck and blah blah blah blah and then going on and just like
Then I guess what I'm trying to say is just don't let it you have the right to be upset bit
I'm not saying anything like that
Just don't want to get to you to where you're all depressed or anything because I'm not again you're being trolled
Welcome to fucking YouTube dude. Like you know what I mean? So just don't let it get you all smile or no
That's all I'm saying. I'm not saying you can't share your emotions. Have your feelings be pissed off
Go say talk your shit. I'm not saying any of that. Just don't let it get you in a spiral. No, that's
It's just really hurt my show more than I like I didn't know it hurt like because like nobody's like I'm actually like almost a
Know it's hard it's hard running a show and I need to tell my body in them because there's been tons of people
Just came through here just since you've been doing you know doing your thing
And we're like dude
What are you doing and you did my fuckers a porn bomb you and you'll let it right back up the next five minutes
And it's just like come on, but you know
I take responsibility for mistakes I've made and I know I've like been not listening to people and I'm
Apologize if you go back and listen to earlier. I was apologizing to people for not
Listening and not doing it fast enough and I just no no you should never have to apologize
That's because it's your show and you're gonna you have to learn the way you're gonna do things
You do it's it's a learning curve. Everybody has speed it has to have a learning curve any creator does right?
We all have shit. We have to learn and we gotta learn our own everybody could tell us, you know
I mean, that's why I don't you ain't gotta apologize for sure
Work through it and don't let it fuck yet. You know what I mean? I think I mean I feel like so much better right now
I've been I feel different than I before about it. Like I'm definitely yeah, I definitely had a turning point
It's definitely a big eye opener for me
I did pray like for for things to be revealed to me and then all of a sudden they were and so I
Just I'm thankful for that and I basically I so I can take the trolling
I don't want anybody that's innocent here to get trolled.
I felt that for a while, but you're not responsible for anybody else and everybody is responsible for themselves.
And if they don't want to be trolled, they don't need to be on the fucking internet.
That's just how that goes.
That's a realistic fact of it, and it sucks.
I want to protect the people that are like, you know, like you and me.
I want to protect you better than I have been.
So as much as I can in my show, right, as long as I can support my show, I want to do
better at that.
Okay.
Thank you.
You have a lot of people that like love you and are loyal to you and they keep coming
back, you know, don't focus on like, um.
Like, I mean, I'm not going to say chose like necessarily, but the ones are trying to get your attention or take away from like your shine just do whatever the fuck you want to do, you know, right?
Exactly.
Because they were on this like as soon as I came on today, like it was like.
45 40 people or something we like had to start timing and people write it because they were just coming on under all these
Sock accounts over and over saying all this shit again, and it's like but I'm like I need to like just like do whack-a-mole with it
Like you know if we see it
We just have to it's got to start every certain people and I know that we have a lot of trolls
It would everyone would be gone if like everybody that just told a little bit
It's like but it's a difference between like, you know, just like really like evil kind of trolling and like you know
The fun good nature to I just want to have a good time here
I don't want to be like some joke, I don't want to be some locale, I don't want to be
some hated person that nobody takes seriously, which is like pretty much happening because
they're repeating the lie often enough, it's becoming the truth to some people.
And it's like, and here I am like, you know, I just have to improve in certain ways too.
You know, I'm going to be trying to improve. Like, you know, I did have a dirty house. I was,
I didn't have dirty nails. I was, you know, drinking too much and I had drunk. I mean,
I still have more improvement to do I'm not perfect and it's like but they're not perfect either
And so it's like how what right do they have to tell me about about that
And it's like it's like to try to be destroying my show and just like intentionally doing things try to get me in trouble
And stuff so I know I have to learn to and I was like I'm I'm learning I'm learning summer
I'm I'm happening slowly. It takes me a long time. I don't make what mistake one time or twice
I make can make a mistake a thousand times before I fucking wise up and it's like maybe that's
personality flower but maybe it's just I really really really need to learn the lesson.
That's for life. That's how I've ever done this. I get drunk and I start crying and I get sensitive
and hurt and stuff like that you know. So I mean I get it but most of these people they don't like
you know show their houses and you don't see what their household is like so you're putting
yourself out there. People are gonna judge everything that you do that's why I barely even.
you know, cam up or whatever, which is good. You're doing, you're, you know, a free soul.
Rebirth, but don't f***ing let them get to you.
Yeah, and the people that are gonna support you they're gonna support you
You know I mean like I it's just no matter what just what you need to do and you don't have to you know
Because listen you can't protect everybody cuz even the people in the chat like love everybody to death
But everybody be doing they own trolling you know I mean everybody has their own issues with people and you can't intervene on every single thing
Cuz you'll be brought the fuck out. But what you can do is decide how you're gonna do your shit
You know what I mean? You dabbed into Happy 2, which, you know, hey, here we are.
You know what I mean? And now you're going to go whatever route you're going to go.
You know what I mean? It's a learning experience. Everybody's got to fucking do it.
But if I have someone that brought me onto the scene though, it was really Betty who was from IPT.
I consider that he was the first person to help give me to the 50 subscribers.
And there's other people not from that community, but I am kind of birthed out of there.
That was the first panel I watched for that I think probably on his show.
You know, I was like, I kind of do like some of that sense of humor, but I don't like some of their audience that are like treating that at the two people like low cows and just like wanting the worst for them, which is like basically that's what basically I see people have been doing like these people are not jokes.
They're like really good interesting people that are putting themselves on camera and maybe embarrassing themselves sometimes, you know, for, you know, maybe views great attention, maybe laughs, maybe just to entertain.
and it's like some are more self-aware than others. I'm a pretty self-aware person. There's so many
people that are the people that are not self-aware they don't know they're being made fun of. I really
am concerned about it because those people don't deserve this abuse. I mean it's like they don't.
They I mean people are people don't end up in this community
The only thing you can do is you can you know you can decide what kind of you know people you have on panel and
Make your rules and do your thing on the far as that goes but again people are gonna
You know people have to be responsible for their own shit because I'll see plenty of times
People come in here they they have their own shit because that it's not even just i b2. This is something i should have to understand
Everybody included me, you know i'm saying i got motherfuckers that do not like me because yep i'm gonna talk my shit
You know what i mean?
We all know that and so they'll be people that'll follow me and then you know
Whatever and me and that maybe me and that person's going back and forth right we're trawling each other
So you can't you can't protect everybody because you know i'm saying like a lot of motherfuckers will start shit and
Once somebody else to fight they fight and you can't do that either, you know what I mean?
Like so just try to create a good environment and you know people who's grown here
So they're responsible for their actions and they're their shit and they they can't oh, you know
Cuz I've seen it happen like I said people start shit other places and then come here and be like
Oh, I don't know what you're talking about like
Yeah, you do so just create a good environment and let them do what they should they're grown
I know okay
I have a very innocent side of me and I have one that's very wise and sometimes a wise one
It's like
Everybody's got a little season on him is what I'm saying. So, you know
I got you and I think thank you for you know always
You know, you've always been really good to me. Yeah
She's very supportive and she's like tells you like it is you know what I mean
And that's where I think we come like, you know all of us kind of like get annoyed at each other
It's like how many times I told you you know, but it's like
Wake up and figure out on your own shit. I'm stubborn
Oh, yeah, we are me too. That's Christina. You know people support me a much shit one minute, you know
One minute. I'll be like, okay. I'm not gonna do drama next minute. I'm like, I'm gonna run this bitch
You know what I mean? This is like, okay. I'm gonna say all the drama. So I mean I get it
You know what I mean? I can't I'm not even saying that's not even that that's not even why I came up here
You know, and that's why I was like, oh, wait a minute. I just always make it known like I've learned the hard way that
I'll be cool with somebody and then get in they beef and then next thing you know the motherfuckers
I'll be a dub being cool again. You know what I mean, and I'm just like yeah, I'm not doing this shit
I'm not here. I'm not nobody's mother. I'm not here to fight anybody's battles
I fight my battles because I have plenty of them to fight
So, you know what I mean now if I see somebody doing something that's just outrageously fucking stupid
Then yeah, I must speak up and say something, but I'm not Greg. Oh, I don't I don't team anybody. I have team me
And that even goes with Katrina and Christine.
And I love Christine, but Christine's her own woman.
She has her own wars.
You know what I mean?
And well, Katrina also starts it with nobody.
So, and I'm just like that because I've learned the hard way on that.
And I'll fuck us up.
Yeah, you just leave yourself.
Leave your ass wide open.
It's not good.
So I just don't do it no more.
Yeah, and I'm like this stuff where I'm like, I'm never going back there again. And I'm like, you know what, at the moment I'll upset and then a couple days later, like a week later, I'm like, calm, I'm like, no, I'm gonna, you know, yeah, people will change their minds if you just stick to something.
But I mean, it does suck people talking about you because you're, you've been nice mostly to and given chances that, you know, to a particular group, but.
You know what? That's the way they have fun. That's the way their troll game is and maybe that's the way of like, you know, grouping up and ganging up and talking about you.
But you do your own thing. You get a lot of variety of people here.
It's not like you go live every day thinking that and hoping that they're gonna be here, you know?
You go live for yourself and other people.
Also, what I'll say is like, you know...
It wasn't like I mean other than like what they were saying about me and stuff
It wasn't really a bad like a show. It's like they had I think you said they were talking about me too like
It was like somebody in the comments said something I didn't hear them particularly
Someone in the comments would bar you up and then they had Sam and his photos too like some
Unflattering but that's like not like that mean and stuff, but it's like but if I'm picture of my nails up and stuff and like
But there's, I mean, it's just like,
they knew I was watching too,
so they maybe were like,
but I don't think it was a bad show.
I like the kind of the music.
I think that they're okay people.
It's like, they hate me for some reason.
I don't know why.
And it's like, and so maybe I reacted
and maybe I gave some back to them and stuff like that.
But I can respect them as people,
but it's like, I feel like they're going after me.
unfair way and it's like they are being fake to me and I appreciate people like
summer that they take with no matter what if we agree or not summer about
everything it's like at least you're speaking your truth to me and it's like
and they were just being phony to me and it's like and I was going for the
okey-doke a little bit but maybe I knew I was you know it's like I'm kind of
self-aware and not self-aware at the same time kind of like you know forgive
I feel like fighting or you know going back and forth sometimes. I like some of the drama. It's hard. It's hard finding the balance sometimes, right?
Yeah, it is because I'm gonna say where I'm like man. I gotta get away from this. But then I'll be like yeah, man
I like I like my drama. You know what I mean? I like raging. I like like crashing the fuck out like I like it
It's fun. You know it's entertaining and that's what I'm here for. I'm here for entertaining and you know what I mean?
Now I like it that I can have a nice little crew
You know I mean like all of us are friends and cool and you know what I mean like we look out for each other
But, you know, I also know that this was, I mean, this was like an internet and, you know,
me and Beatles get into it every now and then and so the next day we're like,
so what? It didn't even happen. You know what I mean? Like,
that we know we're cool with each other. So we can like agree to disagree at the end of the day.
I care about you. I'm not going to, or the both of you, I'm not going to go there and like drag
have we don't have we don't come to an understanding okay fine whatever i move on not a big deal all right
yep that's good i love you guys and it's like yeah what they did is a little bit
revengeful you know maybe they got blocked or they weren't allowed on the panel but for them
to go that far and just not just ignore it just you know stick to your boundaries whatever you
feel like you want to do
So I know they're trying I know they're trying to trigger me because they kept saying like oh, we triggered and we triggered them
And they're so excited about you know like you are you've been you did
Okay, well, it's like well, that's the end. It's like now. It's like
Yeah, now that you know the formula, you know, yeah around it don't let it happen
Yeah, it's like I won't because it's like I gave them enough chances, like too many chances, right?
And it's like they're not gonna, I can't change anybody, but I can maybe help people see and maybe
people like that live through this with me that have watched some of this, I hope it's been educational.
I hope like, you know, maybe it helps people know how to deal with it because it's like I've,
I learned and so maybe everybody learned along with me and it's like that's the beautiful thing
and let's at the end of the day, it's like I want to be about love, I want to be about
improvement and helping people and actually like loving other people not always trying to like
figure other people down like and you know and I want to be you know a good force in people's
lives rather than just a negative thing where it's like everyone look back at my show and say oh that
was you know remember that show that was just a mess I wanted to be like oh that show was pretty
cool and like you know actually you know I had fun there and like it was like one of the
Best shows on YouTube
Here you have all of your the angel AI girls on the panel
I do I really do I really do I'm like I'm so lucky and it's like and if I don't say it enough
I'm just like thank you guys. I'm so blessed like to know so many of you and even the people that
Hate me and stuff like that. You know, I'm maybe blessed to know you too because you've taught me a lot of things too and
Hopefully, I can just be a better person at the end of the day, and we can all become better versions of ourselves.
I think we all have this really great potential in everybody, and it's like, I hope that I can bring it out of people instead of trying to tear them down, and if I ever did it, you know, hurt anybody's feelings or do anything.
Say everything
I did not know that I can show your comments on the stage. That's really weird. How do you know that?
Oh, that's cool. I don't know. I don't know that I can you think let's see like this. Does that show on stage?
No, I don't think so. Let me take off this. Why does it give me the option? It's so weird. Okay. Let's see like
Let's see Jonathan says show on stage. No, it doesn't it gives me the option, but then it won't let me
I don't know. Yeah, same thing with me. I don't let you do it. Yeah
I know they have been changing some StreamYard settings lately and I know that it always
looks a little different.
I'm pulling the X right now is what they are.
Yeah, yesterday I remember when you were like beta. I can't take the link and I was like no
Maybe it's your phone or your boyfriend
Because other people were able to take it but not everybody I went back out
I came back in and I couldn't get into my own stream, you know, so yeah, something was going on yesterday all day
That was weird because
I couldn't get on panel it took me did I ever I made it up there finally I think but
Yeah
After six times
Yeah, but I do have them all yeah, I might try out I have
Prism and stream I have my power chat set up on under stream labs, too
I might I might like do some shows on that because they have some cool
Interface stuff that like stream yard doesn't have but I'll stream yard
I'm able to do backgrounds and stuff now because I have a computer
I can do like the green screen
Again, I can also bring things on the screen share the screen. I can share the screen. I can share my whole screen. Wow
That's crazy. And so, you know, I can put slides PDF files up. I can put extra camera
What's the extra camera do exactly? Oh, I have to upgrade for that one
It says that I think it's like a free one and it's essentially a lot of people using it
So it's the same thing pretty much
the extra camera is if you have an extra camera and then you can get different angles you can switch back and forth to the two cans
That's cool
I'm not going to do that from the car
I want to get another camera for maybe like I could do like an overhead shot for cards and stuff like that
I'm looking into upgrading and stuff
I think somebody that had their show set up like that it was actually pretty good actually
There's now I can guys I'm just got this new computer and stuff
You know I was able to get the computer this month, and it's really really good
And it's like but I have there's like a lot of different settings
I didn't have before because of all my tablet for like almost a year of my show now, and so I'm still
Working it out, but I'm gonna upgrade my equipment still I have a new camera a new
You know, well, I'll get some new stuff and
new microphone and stuff, and new headphones.
I'll make everything really good.
And then I'll also be able to show more entertaining things.
Like I'll be able to share my screen
so maybe I can share some more different content
and stuff with you guys that I wanna share.
I haven't been able to share my screen yet.
So I'm excited for that.
Yay.
That's cool.
I just have to be careful about you know the copyright stuff still I have to make sure I get permission from you know
Anybody I play a video from or something like that because there's some stuff
I want to share but I just don't know the person so it'd be hard to like I don't know if they would just like you know
You know I'm a little bit shy about sharing other content right now, but maybe on my other channel, too
I can do more of that. We'll see
It'll be good. It'll be good. I might broadcast on my other channel sometimes because that's not monetized
And I might do some of the stuff I want to play or we can play movie night or something like that
This can't get well. Yeah, you have your other channel. You never go on there. You're right
Yeah, I can probably do a lot of stuff there. Like, you know, that channel's totally fine
This one is too, but I just like, you know, that channel's not monetized so we can play more music
We can have karaoke night is stuff like some people like and
Just hey, let's stay with me guys. I'm gonna I'm gonna like get better at this. I think I'm always improved
You're doing good. You got monetized fast. You have a lot of people like you're doing good. You're too hard on yourself
Yeah, well because it's like slowed down so much like a last like last month was a pretty good month
Well, that's your competitive side. You're really competitive about this
You got to just kind of let it go and just not think about it too much
You know, whatever happens is you'll go back, you know, I wake up and I'm like, oh, I don't know why I just lost like 10 subscribers
I mean what the fuck did I piss off today? You know, but then you know, and I wake up and there's more it doesn't matter
I'm not gonna like
Analyze it too much. I think we I bet it's getting I scare like a lot of people get scared away
Like new people here
There's not that many new people that come in because they come in and it's like they're like what the fuck is this like it's like
They get either they start the attack all of a sudden they're like what the fuck and so it scares away people right and it's like
So I want people to be like hey, what's this and then I want to stay and hang out and think it's cool
But it's like when there's so much negativity it really will scare away newcomers, right?
Yeah, somebody on your panel that other people don't like and then all of a sudden like other people are pissed off at you and I
Don't know just everybody happy because LD was on like that like their last night
I was you know on that show and everything and also like you know, um stage her was on the panel and
I mean that and not all of them were like putting me down, but
Don't think I mean they're kind of like just trying to like you know when there's a group the kind of group just always agrees
And so like oh, he really does that he really does that and they were just they're believing everything
I don't know if they necessarily work like I
Mean some people are just impressionable and that's kind of sucks
And it's like I could be friends and cool with these people, but they're just they just enjoy
fucking with me or trying to like
hurt me or the show and stuff and I mean it's like however they think you can do that they'll do that and it's like
I just have to have an impenetrable show like I get like a show like
That even if they get in it's like
Bowling what you just use a big term. I'm dead. I don't know that one. What was the word? I said what?
Intramanal. Oh
I don't know. I think you said I want to have an intranamal show. Hi
I'm thank you. I gotta go my friend here. Say hi to Michael
Yeah, have a good show don't worry about it too much. Okay. Thank you. I'm good. I love you. Bye
Bobby to love you
So guys
who knows what will happen it's like you know of course you know it's almost I'm
very forgiving right I just have to put my foot down and say you know if you're
gonna be here you're not gonna be hurting hurting my show or my chat and
or me it's like you know I really take that be respect the host respect the
No dox thing, no slander, no racial language.
Guys, there's ways of saying things
that are not against the COS,
because the COS, it's gonna get probably patrolled more.
If it gets too hard to have a panel, I would regret that,
because I love having an open panel and people coming on.
You know, I've let almost,
I've let form bombers on multiple times, you know?
It's like, even people that have like, you know,
I love some, like Ilya, I love Ilya.
He's pulled him on me twice, but I still love the guy.
I just remember him like from beat is when I started
and I don't think he has bad intentions anymore, but.
Let me have a look at the chat.
I won't keep you here, you know, too much longer.
If, let me see, let me see what's going on in the chat.
We live, we learn, right, Jamie?
Yeah.
No, hold on
Alvaro's hey Alvaro, how are you?
You guys yeah, see this is what I like you guys are talking about sports and the Falcons
I mean, that's cool. They got this get like guys Jamie's so cool. There's so and there's so many people in the chat
Hey, Amanda. Yeah, there's so many good people just be like even if you
Maybe they were honest about some of the trolling and like but he did say like
Hey, but actually I like you and it's like maybe I was like, you know, oh, you know
I like to be liked, you know, especially by people that consider like maybe they considered me an enemy. I like to
But I guess they didn't like really feel that way. They're just trying to
bother me hurt my show and
This looks interesting
Well, that's a shot of Turin, that's what he would look like.
So I don't know if that was like the guy from the Knights Templar or, you know, they say it's Jesus, but
Pretty cool
The guy's name is what was the guy's name? I think if there's a some kind of like
Society named after him. Let me see that guy that was Friday the 13th 19th time Friday the 13th
Templar
So that would be
His name would be
Let's see his name would be
Was it was
Joe Jacques Demolais, okay
That's where you look like Jacques Demolais. Oh
He was then he was, you know, executed as an, and he was a nice Templar, that's Jacques de Molay.
It doesn't look like the shadow of Turin very much, but maybe.
Okay.
And there's something called the De Molay, or something, De Molay Society or something.
It's for like younger people.
I say on the way to Freemasonry.
So, anyway.
And you know, Knights, Templar, they were basically bankers,
but maybe they did have some good intentions.
I don't know, the Knights have a very illustrious
and refutation sometimes, right?
Okay, 33 people in the chat.
How long has it been?
It's been three hours, so I'm gonna wrap it up.
But thank you guys.
I'll be back tonight.
Have a great day.
Thank you for being here.
And...
What channel did it happen on? It happened on JT's channel. I think it's like JT
003 or something like that if someone can you know, you can like if I go have a look at it
You can just see you can just see for yourself how how they treated me and
You know, but
That's their kind of show
Not you hey next you guess you'll never know the channel. I said it was JT 0003. I think it's called okay
You just have to go at JT 0003
Then like he has one video in the main thing
But then go to his lives and that was like there's a live last night
It all it has is a picture of a circus tent a monkey a pair of wings and another circus tent
If you if you guys know how to decode emojis, right?
Yeah, I can actually I can actually share the link alone. I don't know if it's still up, but
I'll, I'll, I'll, I can, I can share the link, so this is the live last night, and you know what, go ahead and say, if you, if you think it's funny, you might, maybe they'll get some new subscribers, and you know, you know,
you know, they say, I'm so unsuccessful, I'm willing to help their channel, you know, it's like, but just, you know, how about go over there and those channels and do shit, and, you know, talk your shit, and not, you know, to me, to my face, on my own channel.
Okay, this is like, I'm done with it.
You're not gonna look in, you know, give me a chance.
No, after, you know, I tried to like give you a chance.
Okay, so, let me just get this link.
Okay, it's still up.
So go ahead and watch it.
And if you like it, you know.
Have fun there, you know, just like if it's your thing, but it's like, you know
I'm not gonna be hateful
For angry or like bitter. I'm not gonna change into like a mean person. I'm gonna be the same
Loving person with good intentions, and I don't want bad for anybody. So here's the link, okay?
So that's fair for motion. I just promoted your show for you guys. Okay, there's JC's channel
You know, I don't think they're bad people. They hate me. I mean, they just hate me
But I'm just like human garbage, but you know what?
They're human beings I love human beings
That
Proceed at your own risk, okay
That live is done. Just oh this one. No their life is done
You took it down
No, it's up
It's a JT. Hold on
This is J. Oh, sorry. It's at JT dash zero zero zero two
Love you guys wish you the best. Okay, you know, you know, and no hard feelings guys
No hard feelings to them or anything, you know, and I forgive you. I forgive you
If you knew I know you didn't even ask for forgiveness. I
Forgive you, okay
but
Be careful how you treat people
Because you don't know who's gonna actually fight back right, okay. Love you guys. Have a good day. I'll see you soon. Okay
Thank you for being here, and thank you for always being a good crowd in my life
Why this time see my other bye guys